It's perfect.
太完美了
Oh, great.
太好了
I'll take it.
我要了
Wonderful. I'm so happy.
噢 我很开心
There's one thing. I'm gonna need some references.
但是有一件事 你需要一位保证人
I don't have any of those.
我没有保证人
Oh, dear, that's serious.
那就麻烦了
I don't know that we can do business together if you don't have references.
如果没有保证人 房子就不能租给你
-Daddy. -What's going on, Isabel?
爸爸 你在搞什么鬼 伊莎贝
I'm moving here.
我要搬到这儿来
To the Valley? Why on earth would you do that?
天啊 你干嘛搬到这鬼地方
Because it's normal.
因为这里很正常
You're normal. You're just--
你也很正常只是 我知道
I know. But I'm not gonna be one anymore.
我知道我不想当女巫
You have no choice in the matter. It's what you are.
你天生就是女巫 没办法选择的
Orange is a great color. Orange is happy.
橘色让人一看就会开心的
Why don't we just paint it yellow?
我看这颜色不开心 黄色不好吗
We can't, we're gonna paint the bathroom yellow.
不好 浴室要漆成黄色的
Since when are we doing that?
谁说要漆成黄色的
They're arguing about paint.
他们小俩口在斗嘴
Yes, I can see that.
我看得出来
Il wanna argue about paint.
我也想为这种小事斗嘴
-With whom? -With someone.
跟谁斗嘴 另一个人呀
Aman?
一个男人
-Yes! -Oh, Isabel.
对 哦 伊莎贝
I'm through with warlocks. They're all like you.
男巫都跟你一样 爸和爸 你跟妈妈结婚以后
Even when you and mom were married...
还对其他女人下魔加
.. you were casting spells on other women.
这是对其他女人下广贺
Your life is total instant gratification, Daddy.
你只追求一时的快乐 对吗
-It's fantastic, isn't it? -No. No, it's not.
那不是很好吗 不不 一点都不好
Because how do you know that anyone really loves you for yourself?
你怎么知道对方真的爱你
It's like those rich men who are never sure why women sleep with them.
就跟女人为了钱和富翁上床一样
But women sleep with them, so it's not really a problem.
只要有人跟找上床就无所谓
I want a man who needs me.
我要一个需要我的男人
Needs you?
需要你
Because he is a completely hopeless mess.
因为他是一个可怜兮今的可怜虫
Oh, no. You're talking about love, aren't you?
哦 你说的是爱情
What do you suppose it's like?
爱情到底是什么东西
Oh, it's simple. You say, "I love you" to someone you want to go home with.
R简单 就是你说你想跟谁上床 你就对他说我爱八
And then when things get messy, you say, "I don't love you anymore."
想甩掉对方 就说我不爱你了
And that's pretty much it.
就这么简单
l feel as if I'm pressed against a glass window.
和爸爸 不简单
It's right there on the other side. I can see it, but 1 can't feel it.
爱情就在另一边看得见却感觉不到
l can't touch it.
遥不可及
-Does your mother know about this? -She disappeared again.
你妈妈知道这事吗 她又消失了
$420.56.
4百20块
Money. Money.
付钱 什么都要钱
That was my last thing as a witch.
这是我最后一次使的魔法
l wanna be like everyone else. Il wanna have friends and I wanna....
我想做个普通人和女伴和逛街
And I wanna go to the Coffee Bean...
然后一起到星巴克喝咖啡
.. where we all discuss our problems, which are absolutely unsolvable.
聊一些没有答案的无聊 话题 自由自在
You can have anything you want. Every woman wants to be a witch.
你要什么就会有什么 谁不想当女巫呢
I don't. wanna feel thwarted.
我就不想女巫
I want days where my hair is affected by weather.
我还想让头发被风给吹乱了
Yeah, hi, what can I get you?
请问你要点什么
Scrambled eggs, please.
请来一份炒蛋
lam through with just snapping my fingers and getting my way.
我不想再靠弹手指 就解决一切事情 知道吗
No breakfast after 11.
11点钟以后不供应早餐
My absolutely last thing.
我保证这是最后一次
Don't do this.
孩子 别傻了
You'll meet someone, you'll get this close.
当你爱的男人 发现你是女巫的时候 那么
-And when he finds out about-- -lf he loves me, he won't care.
他爱我就不会在乎这些
I'm going to get an umbrella.
我需要一把雨伞
Go on. Get yourself one.
变吧 你也可以变把雨伞出来
No, Daddy. No. I mean it. No. Never again.
不 爸爸不要 我下定决心决不施魔法
-You'll get wet. -l hope so.
你会被雨淋湿的 那样最好
I know what you're gonna say. I'm a mess.
我就知道 我真是倒性透了
Get a grip, Jack. Get a grip.
杰克 振作点
Il can't help it.
我振作不起来呀
You look great.
帅极了
-l look great? -Yeah.
真的吗 真的
l always look great. That's a given.
我天生就是个大帅哥啊 那当然
-And the important thing is.... -What?
重要的是什么
I have no idea what the important thing is.
我不明白
I'm telling you, I feel like I'm about to go out of my mind.
实话告诉你 我都快疯了
You know, I want my life back. Okay? I want my wife and my house.
这次我真的毁了 我的老婆和房子都没了
Il wanna be a movie star again. ! mean, what the hell happened, Richie?
我的电影也不卖座 这到底出了什么问题
Things were going so great for a while.
本来还好好的 怎么会这样呢
Last Year in Katmandu. It cost 140 mil to make.
西藏大疯狂 一亿四千万的成本 哦 我的天啊
Grossed 1.6. The only DVD to sell no copies.
票房只有一百六十万 连一片D VD都卖不出去
We probably shouldn't have shot it in black-and-white.
我们不应该拍这黑白片
But now you're gonna do a television series and it's gonna be a hit.
如果你拍电视剧的话 一定会大红大紫的
So pull yourself together, man, because you look like Don Johnson.
你看起来就跟金城武一样
-But in a bad way. -Okay, I got it.
只是你长得 没他那么遇
-I'll pull myself together. -Let's go.
好点吗 我知道 我们走吧 我会振作起来的
And don't get all nice on me. Be mean.
记住 别装好人 要摆架子
I'm gonna be mean.
对摆架子 别忘了摆摆架子啊
Hit me. There you go.
好了 给我一巴掌
You're the Jackerator, baby. Let's go. Let's go. Come on.
好样的 你最棒 我们走
Yo, gentlemen. How are you? Oh!
嘿 你们好 你好
-Hi, I'm Jack. -Oh. Huge fan. Huge.
我是杰克 你好 你好
-How are the kids, guys? -Great.
我是你的大影迷 孩子们好吗
Good. Well, let's cut the chitchat.
很好
-Thank you. I'm Jack, by the way. -Nina.
咱们就废话少说吧
-Jack wants to do the show. -That's great.
杰克想演电视剧 太好了
-l wanna do it. -That's great. That's terrific.
我想要演 太好了
He only has one concern.
他只担心一件事
We had the same concern.
放心吧
But we think everyone's forgotten about Last Year in Katmandu.
观众们都已经忘了 西藏大疯狂了
Unless they saw it.
除非他们去看过
His concern is...
他担心
.. the witch has all the fun.
女巫会变成主角
You will be fun.
你才是主角
We're changing it from the original.
我们会做一些更改
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Don't all go crazy. Okay? I mean, it is Bewitched.
等等 你们不要乱改 神仙家庭 这个
I mean, Samantha should be strong. Right? This should be a two-hander.
这个戏 珊曼莎这角色很重要 男女主角的戏份一样多
Oh, my God. Huh? Hey. What a relief.
我们知道 那我们就放心了
l was worried because Larry told me you'd want to tilt the show toward you--
赖瑞还跟我说 你本来想独挑大梁的
Stu, Stu.
哦 不是 史都
We gotta have a great ensemble is what I'm thinking. You know?
不是 这跟六人行一样 是大捕头的戏
Endora, the next-door neighbors, all those crazy family members.
你们知道吗 安多拉 邻居和其它的家人
Who's gonna play Uncle Arthur? Huh? l used to love Uncle Arthur.
谁来演阿瑟叔叔 我最爱阿瑟叔示了
Well, we're looking for Uncle Arthur.
我们会找到适合的人选的
-Your table's ready. -Thank you.
请入座吧 谢谢
I don't know if you remember...
他每次从镜子里面走出来
..but when he'd appear in the mirror, it would crack. It would always crack.
镜子都会破的 大家都知道会破
And you knew it was coming, and yet, every time it happened...
不过我每次看到这一幕的时候
..[ laughed and I laughed and I laughed.
还是会笑到不行 真的是太好笑了
-Can I talk to you? -l loved it.
我要跟你说句话
"Hi, Sammy."
你好呀 阿莎 你好啊
One second, fellas. We'll meet you guys at the table, all right?
我们待会在餐桌上见 好了吗 再见
Hey, I like those guys. What?
我喜欢他们 你干付么
-You're being a pussy. -What?
你是个配角 什么
You're being a pussy, pussy, pussy!
你是个大配角
No, I'm not! I want the show to be good.
不是 我只是很好合作罢了
You want the show to be-- You know what?
杰克 你给我听好了
Jack Wyatt's doing TV now because his film career ate it!
你的电影不卖座 所以才来演电视
And he's not even the clear star of his own show.
而且还不是第一男主角 你是个配角
Jack, screw Uncle Arthur. Hell, screw ensembles, man.
去他的阿瑟叔叔去他的安得 让他们通通见鬼去吧
-I'm being a pussy. -Yes.
我只是个配角 没错
If this show tanks, you'll be on Hollywood Squares for 10 years.
但如果这次失败了 你就永远不得翻身了
You will also be the mayor of Pussytown.
你会永远只是一个最大的配角
I don't wanna be the mayor
我可不想当配角 听着
Get in there and be the sheriff of Ballsville.
你一定要当这个狠角色
-All right? -Okay.
知道吗 知道
-Bring it.
尽管摆大架子 好吧
Let's go.
上吧
-Stop that. -Sorry, sorry.
你住手啊你
Sorry, guys, where were we?
抱歉 我们说到哪儿了
Couple of big names are available for Samantha.
有几个大明星想演珊曼落
-To hell with that. -Yeah.
去他的大明星 就是啊
I want an unknown in the lead. All right?
我要找一个菜鸟演员
A hot new face that's gonna look good and set me up.
我要一个大花瓶在旁边陪衬我
Because I have worked my ass off to the bone for too long...
多不容易啊 我努力了这么多年
..to build up the brand value of the name Jack Wyatt!
才打响杰克怀特这个牌子 你们知不知道我很不容易啊
-This show has one star. -And I want three trailers.
这部戏只有一个明星 我要三间专用休息的拖车
Nobody in television has three trailers.
没有人可以用三间休息拖车
He wants them, you get them.
不给就拉倒
And l want my own makeup team in matching jumpsuits.
我要专用的造型小组 还要一只花鸥
And a leopard! l want a pet leopard.
一只花鹏
With a diamond-studded collar. Real diamonds.
它要戴着 镶看钻石的项圈 懂吗
-That's enough, Jack. -And a cake.
够了 杰克
A two-story-high cake. Every Wednesday's Cake Day.
我还要 两层楼高的蛋糕 两层楼高的
And we're gonna bring it out...
每周三都是蛋糕日
..and we're gonna pretend it's a surprise.
假装这是个惊喜
Because it's Cake Day.
然后切和蛋糕
We get it, Jack.
每周三都是蛋糕日
If we have a leopard, we're gonna have major insurance issues.
够了 杰克 保险公司会对花鹏有意见
We're willing to give on the leopard.
这件事可以商量
It's getting hard to breathe.
我快跨不过气来了
-Should I be writing this down? -No.
要不要抄下来呢 不要
So this should be fun. Huh? Right?
这一定很好玩 对吧 是吗
l used to have the biggest crush on Elizabeth Montgomery when I was 10.
我小时候 最爱看 神仙家庭这部戏了很好看的
-We all did. -The nose. I mean...
大家都一样 珊曼莎的鼻子 我是指
It's not gonna be easy finding a nobody to play Samantha.
如果找一个新人 演她并不容易
Be the sheriff.
摆架子
Well, Jack Wyatt says get it done, y'all.
大明星杰克说了算数 听见了没有
Hey, I'm turning on the sprinklers in my front yard.
嘿 我能打得开前院的酒水器了
Dimming up.
开灯
Dimming down.
关灯
Wow!
哇
I don't think you quite understand.
你不明白
This is very confusing.
这真的很复杂
I put the black cable in the red plug like they said...
我把黑线搬进红色的插头 可是还是没有画面
..and the screen is still blue.
真不知道 怎么回事
I'm here to give you cable.
我是来帮你接第四台的
Oh, thank you, I already have some.
哦 谢谢 我已经有了
Hello? Don't go away, please.
喂 不要挂 不要挂断 哦
To heck with all this bunk!
真讨厌 真烦人
There.
全好了
Let's just keep this between us, Lucinda.
圳露 别说出去嗪
ls your self-esteem low because you aren't participating in the real world?
你有没有感觉和现实脱离 感到没有自信吗
Yes, my self-esteem is very low.
对呀 我真的非常没有自信
Well, let's face it, you need a job.
面对现实吧 你需要工作
There's something I have to tell you, Darrin.
我有件事要告诉你
-I'm a witch.
戴伦 我是个女巫 我是个女巫
lam a witch.
我是一个女巫
Good. Good.
很好 很好
Oh, my goodness.
嗪 我的天啊
God bless you.
天啊 就是你
Don't look, but Jack Wyatt is staring at you.
别看 杰克怀特在看你呢
My heart's pounding, and l am feeling very weird tingles.
我的心跳加速 全身起鸡皮疙将
I know. He makes me sick too.
我也觉得他挺恶心的
You know him?
你认识他吗
Jack Wyatt? The actor?
杰克怀特 那个破演员
Where have you been?
你是外星人吗
-May I join you? -Sure.
你不介意吗 不介意
Thank you.
我知道 谢谢你
Look, I've never done this before.
听我说 我从没做过这种事
How would you like to be ona television show?
你想不想演电视剧 请问你贵姓
-Ms.... -Bigelow.
你叫什么
Bigelow?
毕格罗
Isabel Bigelow.
伊莎贝毕格罗
What do you think? Wanna be a famous actress?
你想不想当演员
-Me? -Yeah.
我 对
-An actress?
当演员 对
Il can't act.
我又不会演戏
Anyone can act.
连猫和狗都会演戏
If l can act, you can act.
连我都会演戏 你一定行
Amen.
一点也没错
I think those people over there just finished their plate of hummus.
你难道没有看见 那桌的客人都吃完了
You might wanna help them by clearing it. Thank you.
你最好去收一下盘子 谢谢
So, Isabel Bigelow, do you have a job?
伊莎贝 现在你有工作吗
-No. -Are you rich?
没有 你有钱吗
Because I am.
我很有钱
I'm extremely wealthy.
我很有钱的
Which I'm about to prove to you by taking care of this bill...
我证明给你看啊 我帮你付帐吧
..for two dollars...
两块 三毛一
..and 31 cents.
你看 我给你付
-Wow. -Yeah. "Wow" is right.
是 没错
l have to remember to get some money.
我得记得想办法弄点钱
Yeah.
是啊
So do you wanna be rich and famous?
那么 你想发财成名吗
I just wanna be normal.
我只想做个正常人
Well, acting is better than normal.
演戏比做正常人更好啊
Yeah. You get to pretend to be normal.
你可以演一个正常人
And then if you're good, you become a big star...
演得好就可以当大了明星
-...and guess what happens. -What?
然后你猜会怎么样
You snap your fingers and pretty much anything you want materializes.
弹一弹手指 想要什么 就有什么了 真的
Oh, no. No, no, no.
不 不要
Il have that now. It's what I'm giving up.
我就是想戒掉这个坏习惯
Oh, it was lovely to meet you.
哦 很高兴认识你
You seem very sweet and unkempt and troubled.
你人很好 既录遇又可怜兮兮的
Hey, hey, hey. Those are bad things to say to a person.
嘿 那并不是赞美啊
Oh, no, they aren't.
卫 不是呀
I think the fact that you're a hopeless mess is very refreshing.
我觉得你可怜兮今的 这很好呀
It moves me.
我很感动
-lsabel Bigelow. -Yes?
伊莎贝毕格罗 什么事
I need you.
我需要你
What did you say?
哦 你说什么
-l said, need you. -You need me?
我说我需要你 你需要我
I need you.
我需要你
You don't have to come audition.
你不必来试镜头
Just come and show everyone what you look like when you do it.
只要让大家看你到你扭鼻子就行了
Like this?
像这样吗
Uncanny.
特别像
-It's identical. -l told you.
一模一样 我就说吗
You go, girl!
很好
We would just like you to read the script.
我们想请你读剧本
Start on page 13. Should be marked there.
从十三页开始 知道了吗
Read it?
你要我读吗 对
Yeah. We want an idea of what it could sound like.
是的 我们要听见你的声音 说出来
"Int., honeymoon suite, night-- Dash, night.
内景 蜜月套房 夜戏
Darrin and Samantha are sitting on the bed."
戴伦和珊曼莎坐在床上
Someone's not too bright.
好像不是很聪明
Just.... Just read the part that says "Samantha."
只要念珊曼莎的台词就好了
"Darrin, I know it's our honeymoon, but there's something I have to tell you.
戴伦 我知道我们在度蜜月 我有件事要告诉你
I'm a witch."
我是个女巫
-I'm not a witch. -Yeah, exactly.
我不是个女巫
-No, you're giving it up. -Who told you?
对 没错 你不想当女巫对吧
You're about to. On the next page.
你从哪里知道的 是从剧本的下一页
It's Bewitched. The TV show. We're redoing it.
我们要重拍电视剧 神仙家庭 啊
Oh, I wasn't allowed to watch Bewitched.
你看 我从来没有看过神仙家庭
Who wasn't allowed to watch Bewitched?
有人没看过吗 我没有
-That's great, Jack. -That's great.
太好了 杰克 很好
Well, I play a mortal. And I'm in love with you.
我演一个凡人 我爱上你
And I don't care that you're a witch.
还有 我不在乎你是女巫
You don't care?
你不在乎
No? Is that true?
真的还假的
Now go ahead and read the lines.
继续 念台词 我陪着你念
I'll read with you. We'll do it together.
我跟你对戏
Randall? Where are you? Yes. Thank you.
兰道 人呢 好的 谢谢
This'll be easy.
很简单
-Here? -Yeah.
是这儿吗 对
I'm a witch, Darrin.
我是一个女巫
A house-haunting, broomstick-flying, cauldron-stirring witch!
骑着扫曲装神弄鬼的女巫
Great. Great.
太好了 很好
Know what? Let's put the script down, let's put it away, and we'll improvise.
别看剧本 我们即兴表演 好不好吗
Jack. That was only one line.
杰克 她只念了一名台词啊
Not a big deal.
没关系
Go ahead, just set it down.
把剧本给我
Randall.
兰道
I'm gonna ask you questions, just answer them as if you're a witch.
假装你是女巫 然后回答我的问题 即兴的 好吗
-Sure. -Yeah.
好的 来吧
Were your parents in the witch business?
你父母也是巫师吗
Both of them. My mother fixed the 1986 World Series.
俩个都是86年的 职棒赛是我妈妈搞的鬼
-Funny. -Make a note of that.
很有趣 这一句抄下来
Do you carry around poison apples, like in Snow White?
你会不会像白雪公主那样 有毒苹果呢
Oh, no, you have to have a permit for a poison apple.
没有 作毒苹果需要许可证
Permit? Okay, good to know.
许可证 很好 这倒新鲜
That's good.
这一句也非常好
Oh, what's it like to date a warlock?
那么你跟男巫是每么样约会的
Oh! Horrible.
喊 太可怕了
They're self-centered, not very bright, and all that feel-good-in-the-moment.
他们特别自私又很条 而且只贪图享乐
Not at all like you.
跟你完全不一样
What's so funny?
有什么好笑的
Nothing, J-Bone.
没事
What's your favorite spell?
你最喜欢什么魔法
Oh, no, I don't like to talk about that because I'm quitting and--
哦 我不想谈了 因为我想要戒掉
No, talking about it just makes it harder, so....
要是一直谈下去会戒不掉的 很好
Are you sure you never saw Bewitched?
你真的没看过 神仙家庭
She's incredibly dialed-in.
她真的很入戏啊
-Can l ask a question? -Sure.
我想问个问题 请问
How much longer do we have to do this for?
我们还要这么做多久呀
Oh, this? We're almost done with this.
哦 就快好了 是不是啊
I mean, if you do the show, we'll be together forever.
如果你答应演出的话 我们就会永远在一起的
-You and I? -Would you please do the show?
你跟我 求求你演这部戏吧
-What? This show? -This show.
这部电视剧吗 对
-The Bewitched show? -Absolutely.
神仙家庭 吗 没错
We'll work together. We'll be partners.
可以跟我一起合作
Be my TV wife.
做我的老婆
-This is very complicated. -Marry me.
哦 这太突然了 嫁给我
Say yes.
说你愿意吧
What are you doing, Isabel?
喊 我这是在干什么
Easy answer.
答案很简单
-Yes. -Yes!
我愿意 太好了
Great. Thank you.
太棒了 谢谢你
Okay. Let's make the deal. Right?
可以吗 就那么说定了
Once upon a time, there was a typical American girl...
从前有一个平凡的美国女孩
...who happened to bump into a typical red-blooded American boy.
撞到一个平凡的热血青年
And she bumped into him, and bumped into him.
她撞到他 他又撞到她
So they decided they'd better sit down and talk this over...
他们决定聊天
...before they had an accident.
以免再发生意外
They became good friends.
他们一见钟情
-Hi! -Hello?
路 你好
They brought this while you were out. I said I'd bring it over.
有人送你这个 我蔡你代收了
I'm your neighbor, Maria Kelly.
我是你的邻居玛莉亚
-Come in! -Thank you.
谢谢你 快请进
What is all this stuff?
这是什么东西
I just got the most amazing job.
我找到很棒的工作了
I'm gonna be Samantha on Bewitched. They're redoing it.
我要出演珊曼莎 他们要重拍 神仙家庭
Are you an actress?
你是演员吗
I guess lam.
我猜是吧
I love that show. Is that the one about the genie?
那部戏讲的是仙女 对吧
-No. -This is so exciting!
哦 真是太兴奋了
Oh! There you are. Come here. This is you!
哦 快来看 那就是你
Oh, I love this show.
我最爱这个戏了
You know it?
你看过吗
Watched it every night. Love the song. Perfect.
主题曲也很好听 每天晚上都看
There you are! You're great! Look at the nose!
那就是你 看看她的鼻子
I hope you can do that.
这很难的 你会吗
That's how I got the job. Wriggling my nose.
我就是靠这一招得到这一个角色的
-Really? -It's easy.
真的假的 真的
Who's gonna play your husband?
谁演你的老公啊
-Jack Wyatt. -Oh, my God.
杰克怀特 哦 我的天啊
He believes in me. He wants to be partners with me. Listen to this:
他相信我 他想跟我合作
"Looking forward to working with you, Isabel.
你听着 我很期待跟你合作
Isn't that amazing?
很棒吧
He's single. It's in all the tabloids. His wife dumped him.
他是黄金单身汉哦 小报说他被老婆用了
-ls that true? -Yes!
真的吗 真的
Oh, my gosh.
卫 我天啊
I don't know why we're doing this, but it's fun.
我真搞不懂了
I know!
不过真很好玩
Although, you shouldn't get involved with someone you're working with.
是啊 不过你最好 别跟同事谈恋爱
It can destroy your references. I'm a career counselor and--
这会影响你的履历的 真的相信我
Well, that's the only reason I took the job.
我演这部电视剧就是为了他
He is the cutest mess you have ever seen. He is hopeless.
他是最可爱的可怜虫他可怜兮兮的 他简直是无药可救了
Oh, gosh, he's beyond mortal.
我真的不知道该怎么办了
My father would never approve.
我爸爸一定会反对的
Oh. Well.
卫 没人
l won't?
是吗
Daddy. Hi.
和爸爸
What are you doing here?
你跑来干什么
Hello, Isabel. Love the hat.
你好 伊莎贝 好漂亮的帽子
And who is this?
这位美女是谁呀
This is my father.
他是我爸爸
This is Maria Kelly.
这是玛莉亚
How witchy was that? We talk about your father and he turns up.
怎么会这么巧 说他 他就到了
Maria is my neighbor.
玛莉亚是我的邻居
Nigel Bigelow. Enchanté.
奈吉上毕格罗 幸会
Okay.
你好
And what won't I approve of?
你刚才说我反对什么
A man Isabel thinks is cute.
伊莎贝喜欢上一个男人
I'm completely against it.
我坚决反对
I'm gonna be an actress in a television series.
我准备要出演一部电视剧
She's gonna play Samantha on Bewitched.
她要出演 神仙家庭
Bewitched? That's an insult to our way of life.
神仙家庭” 真是丢我们家的脸
Your dad is a hoot.
你爸爸好风趣哦
I'm gonna take one of these, because you got a lot.
你不介意我拿一个吧
Oh, sure.
哦 尽管拿 好吧
Anyway, if anyone's robbing my house, let me know. I'll do the same for you.
如果有人找我 你可要告诉我 街坊邻居可要互相帮忙啊
Oh! And if you get a date that has a friend...
哦 如果你钓到的男人有朋友
.. make sure he's not secretly married before you call me.
先确定他没结婚再告诉我
-Bye, Nigel. -Bye, Maria.
再见 奈吉 再见 玛莉亚
Bye, Maria.
再见 玛莉亚
Why can't you be happy for me?
你为什么就不替我高兴呢
In less than a week I have become a rich and famous actress...
我马上就要变成一个出名的明星了
.. living in a house I don't even have to pay rent for...
成名以后 住的房子不必担心付房租
.. Just like every other person in the world.
就跟世界上每个人都一样
Why wouldn't l be happy?
我有什么好高兴的
You've turned your back on your own kind...
伊莎贝 你背叛家庭不说
..and now you live down the street from a Denny's.
还要搬到这种鬼地方来
Don't make fun of my life. I could make fun of your life.
别取笑我 我也可以取笑你的
So, what about this man?
那么 谈谈你喜欢的男人
No, am not telling you anything anymore, you're too negative.
不我才不呢 你一定会说坏话的
One morning, ! shot a lion in my pajamas.
有一天我穿睡衣打死一头老虎
What he was doing in my pajamas, lll never know.
后来我才发现是我家那只母老虎
Uncle Arthur. Classic.
哦 阿瑟叔叔实在太好玩了
Your brand of low comedy always did appeal to adolescent mentality.
对不起 你说的笑话实在是太冷了
! won't do it.
我不能对她施魔法
Speaking of traveling, remember that time....
那次我们在巴黎约会 你还记得吗
Maybe I will.
这是最后一次
--sent over from Europe. It's simply gorgeous.
欧洲的风景真美的
It reminds me of the one in California.
让我想起加州
Lucinda, you really should be watching this.
哦 露露 你应该看看啊
I'm only trying to say that you broke your promise.
你知道吗 你违背了诺言
You gave me your word, no more....
你向我保证不再
Stuff.
施魔法 是的
It's a little harder to break the habit than I thought.
这坏习惯很难改掉
Well, you can do it. I've got a lot of faith in you.
你一定能改掉 我对你有信心
Thank you, darling.
谢谢你 老公
Ladies and gentlemen...
女士们 先生们
.. please welcome the star of the new Bewitched:
请欢迎 神仙家庭 男主角
I didn't expect you guys to be here.
没想到会有那么多的记者啊
Okay, as you know, we're here for Bewitched.
好了 这是 神仙家庭 的记者会
But it's not the same Bewitched that you remember. It's being retooled.
这不是旧版的 神仙家庭 而是全新的版本
But there is going to be a Samantha?
剧中还有珊曼莎吗
Of course. Isabel, can you come out here?
当然曼 伊莎贝 出来吧
Be brave. You look beautiful.
勇敢点 你很美
Ladies and gentlemen of the press...
各位记者先生小姐
.I'd like you to meet the talented and delightful Ms. Isabel Bigelow.
才华洋溢 美丽大方的 伊莎贝毕格罗小姐
Say hello to the people, Isabel.
向大家打个招呼
Hello.
你们好
No, no, into the microphone. Here. Here.
对着麦克风说
-Hello. -That's enough.
大家好 好了
Now do that thing that you do.
来扭鼻子那一招吧
Isn't that great?
很棒吧
That was great. Great. Just stand there.
太棒了 可以站到一边了
And guess who's playing Endora.
大家猜猜谁要演安多拉
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome the great, the legendary...
各位先生女士 请欢迎传奇性老牌影星
..Miss Iris Smythson, as my mother-in-law.
艾莉丝史密森 没错
That's right.
热烈欢迎 艾莉丝史密森
Iris Smythson. Iris?
艾莉丝 艾莉丝呢
-lris? -All right, what's going on?
艾莉丝 发生什么事了
lris Smythson.
艾莉丝史密森
And of course she hates me. Don't you?
她讨厌我 对不对
Anything you say, Jerry.
你说了算 杰利
Jack. See what 1 mean? That's a joke, right?
是杰克 看见了吧 这是笑话 对吧
Endora used to refer to Darrin as Derwood.
安多拉老是把戴伦叫成戴伍
No, I just forgot your name.
我真是忘了你的名字
But the news here isn't Iris Smythson...
焦点并不是艾莉丝史密森
.. after the twin disasters of his last movie...
两部电影失利后 决定进军小屏幕
..and a messy split from his wife, Sheila...
也不是他和老婆席拉
...who's already found someone new...
结婚一年半
.. after a marriage that lasted only 19 months.
就劳燕分飞
Didn't she leave him for a snowboarder‘underwear model?
席拉跟滑雪选手兼内衣男模跑了
He's a moronjidiot.
他是个白痴兼笨猪
-That's right. -Aren't they living together?
没错 他们已经住在一起了
Yes, in my house! My house that bought before I even met her.
是的 住在我家 住在我认识她以前买的房子里面
And she won't move or sign the divorce papers.
她不肯搬家也不肯签离婚证书
The big news is the surprise casting of an unknown as Samantha.
焦点是饰演珊曼莎的 是个不知名的演员
Her name is Isabel Bigelow...
她叫伊莎贝毕格罗
..and she's quite the charmer, isn't she?
她很迷人 对吧
-That's magic. -So, what's Jack Wyatt thinking?
魔力四射啊 杰克到底在想什么
"My career has tanked, so I'Il fix it by playing Darrin"?
他怎么会演没人爱的戴伦
Plus, he did not look well.
而且他的气色很差
Not look well? I look fine.
胡说 我的脸色好得很
I'm extremely healthy.
我是个健康的宝宝
Richie. Richie.
该死
What am I gonna do with you?
瑞奇 你把我给害惨了
Boy.
老天节
This is Richie.
我是瑞奇
Richie. Why'd you talk me into doing this show? Huh?
瑞奇 你怎么叫我演这部破电视剧啊
What was I thinking? What were you thinking?
你知道别人怎么说我吗 你知不知道
Cast a nobody. You're completely safe.
找个不知名的演员 就什么事都没有了
Richie, can't you come over here? I could use a little support on this one.
你必须马上过来 安慰我
Jack, I can't because I'm about to step into a meeting with the head of NBC.
杰克 不行图 我得跟电视台主管开会
lll be right there! One second.
开完会后 才能来你别急啊
Look, I don't know if you know this, but I'm Darrin, okay?
听着 也许你没摘清楚 他们叫我演戴伦 知道吗
They replaced Darrin on the original Bewitched and no one noticed!
当年他们把演戴伦的演员给换掩了 可谁也没注意到 换掉了
Nobody is going to replace you.
没有人会把你换掉的
I'm Darrin! How did this happen?!
我是没人爱的戴伦 这下惨了
Hold the work!
大家安静 开始
Once upon a time, there was a typical red-blooded American boy...
从前有一位平凡的热血青年
...who happened to bump into a typical American girl.
撞到一位平凡的美国女孩
And, cut!
好停
-Jack, Jack. -How was I? How was I?
我演得怎么样 怎么样啊
-You were wonderful, man. -So good.
棒极了
-Don't lie to me. -No. My ribs hurt.
真厉害啊 别哄我了
It's what I get paid to do.
我笑到肚子都痛了
Jack? Uno mas? From the top?
再来一次
Did you see what happened? Good stuff.
再来一次 会比这次好
Moving on!
下一场
You know it, dude. Nice one.
好 你演得非常好
Here we go. Off to a good start, huh?
准备了 好的开始是成功的一半
And after a while, he did what any red-blooded American boy would do.
过了不久 他就做了 每个热血青年 都会做的事
Samantha, will you marry me?
珊曼莎 你愿意嫁给我吗
Cut!
停
Great! Beautiful. That was good.
太好了 你演得太好了
That was good.
你演得真好
-Action. -You're a witch?
开始 你是个女巫
And you waited until our wedding night to tell me?
可你到了新婚之夜才告诉我 我真是
I don't believe this! Oh, golly!
我真不敢相信 啊
Samantha.
珊曼莎
Cut! Cut!
停 停
Joey, for God's sake.
你干什么呢
Are you trying to kill everyone? Because we can't breathe.
烟那么浓 想把大家哈死吗 你要早一点进内电效果知道了吗
And what's going on with the lightning?
艾莉丝
You can't nod to the audience in the show. It just breaks the reality.
你不能只对着观众点头啦 明白吗
What?
知道了吗 什么
You can't nod to them. You can't do....
你不能只对观众点头
Go sit in your chair. Back to your chair.
你给我乖乖坐回去
All right, but--
回去坐好 我说了
Take two up. Rolling!
第二次 开机
You're a witch? And you waited until our wedding night to tell me?
你是个女巫 可你等到新婚之夜才告诉我 啊
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信 这是怎么回事啊
What's going on?
发生什么事了
Samantha.
珊曼莎
Why is she waving?
怎么回事 她干嘛要挥手呀
Who are you?
你是谁
lam Samantha's mother, Endora.
我是珊曼莎的妈妈 安多拉
A mortal? You married a mortal?
你嫁给了一个凡人
Oh, my poor, poor baby. This is just horrifying.
可怜的女儿 这太惨了
I think I need a drink.
我得喝杯酒
Freeze!
别动
Unfreeze!
可以动了
What a shame you didn't drink it.
可异你没喝下去
If you had, perhaps you could've spent your wedding night as a bullfrog.
不然你就会变成一只大牛蛙
Don't worry, Samantha. I won't do it. Witch's honor.
放心 我不会那么狠 女巫的保证
My darling, we are quicksilver.
我们来无影 去无踪
We're a fleeting shadow.
就像是
We're a distant sound.
天上的仙女
-That's your mother? -We live on the wind...
那是你老妈
..in the sparkle of a star.
我们是天仙下凡
And you want to trade all that for an acre of crabgrass?
你却为了这傻蛋放弃这一切
Did she just call me an acre of crabgrass?
她既然加我是个傻瓜
Deal with it, Derwood.
没错 你是个大乌龟
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢大家 谢谢大家
Thank you!
谢谢
l want a piece of the show. Why?
我要分红 为什么
Because I put this thing together, that's why.
因为这是我的点子
Because Jack Wyatt doesn't parallel park without checking with me.
没有我的同意 杰克连屁都不敢放
Let me call you back. J-Bone!
我再打给你 好吗
You're crushing it, baby. Absolutely crushing it.
杰克 你演得棒极了 我是说真的
- think we got something. -It's exciting.
这次很有搞头 真的很棒
-How's Isabel doing? -She's perfect.
我知道 她真是太棒了
She looks hot and she lets you score like a madman.
太完美了 她是个大花瓶 你才是主角
I know. She's great.
我知道 她真是太棒了
I can't believe you found her.
她做花瓶太好了
You think she's gonna notice?
她会在意吗
What? That she doesn't have a part? Not a chance. She's clueless.
她嫌戏少 不 她才没那么聪明呢
Plus, I think she's got a little thing for you.
而且她很崇拜你
It's freaking pathetic.
真的
-You think so? -Yes.
真的假的 真的
Man, that would be--
那对她会是
Such a nightmare. I know. Can you imagine?
一场恶梦 是的
Although, she does have kind of a cute little back end on her.
不过她的身材倒是一流的
l wouldn't kick her out of bed for eating a box of crackers.
要是她主动投怀送抱 你不用拒绝
Isabel?
伊莎贝
-Did she hear us? -Not a chance.
她听到了了吗 不可能
A couple of changes to the script.
剧本有一些修改
It was running a little long, so we cut your lines.
戏拖得太长 你的台词被删掉了 这样更好
Think of it this way, it's less to memorize.
这样的话 你就不必背台词了
Sorry.
对不起
Lunch!
嘿 吃饭了
Isabel!
伊莎贝
I feel like a fool. A big, stupid, sad fool, and yet I'm angry as well.
我觉得自己真是个大猪头 我快被气炸了 怎么会是这样呢
What's going on?
杰克 是个大混蛋
Let's set fire to his trailer. Let's just do it.
我们放火把他的拖车给烧了 好吗 你说什么
Isabel, this is awesome! You're on TV.
伊莎贝你好棒啊 你上电视了 知道吗
He lied to me.
他驹了我
He tricked me. He said he needed me.
他明明说他需要我
When all he needed was someone to stand next to him...
他其实 只需要一个大花瓶
.. while he says his stupid clever lines.
站在他旁边听他讲冷笑话
-Hi, I'm Maria. -Nina.
路 我是玛莉亚 我是妮娜
He seemed so messy and sincere. But really, he's just a big fake.
他看起来可怜今今 忠厚老实 骨子里却是个大坏蛋
We could electrocute him. There's tons of wires around here.
我们可以用电线把他电死
l wanna cry, l wanna break things. I wanna hurt him.
我现在好想哭 我好生气 我好想伤害他
Yet there's a part of me that still has a small amount of feeling for him.
但是我对他还是有一点感情
How can this be?
怎么会是这样呢
When my first husband left me, l wanted to cut the brakes in his car...
我第一任丈夫甩掉我的时候 我也希望他出车祸
.. but instead we ended up having sex on the elliptical machine.
但结果我们却在健身房绰绵起来
He doesn't understand who he's dealing with. He has no idea.
他不知道我是什么人 他根本 根本不知道我的厉害
Look, you have three options:
听着 你有三个选择
You put up with it...
忍下这口气
quit...
辞职不干
..or get mad.
再就是翻脸
What would Samantha do?
珊曼莎会怎么做
She chose mad, right?
她选择翻脸 对吧
Okay, everybody, settle down.
大家安静
Okay, working very quietly, like little mice.
大家要像老鼠一样的安静
I don't want to see or hear what you're doing.
别让我听到你们半点声音
Okay, so, Isabel, just to refresh your memory, Darrin's ex-girlfriend--
好了 伊莎贝 这场戏 是讲戴伦的前女友
l read the script.
我读过剧本
Okay. Well, let's just go over it one more time.
好 那就再排练一遍
Oh, and we rehearsed it a lot.
哦 我们排练很多遍了
Darrin's ex-girlfriend has invited you both over for dinner.
戴伦的前女友请他去吃饭
And Darrin forced you to come with him--
戴伦 她逼你和他一起去
He tricked me. Because he is a self-centered has-been.
他骗了我 他是个自私的坏演员
No, no, baby, that's not it. No.
不 不是啦 亲爱的 不是这样 不对
Because he wants his dog back, and then Darrin says his line:
他要拿回他的狗 他说 那是我的狗
-"It's my dog. -It's my dog.
那是我的狗 我要拿回来
-l want him back." -l want him back.
那是我的狗 对
It always kills me, Jack. You ready to go?
这名台词特别好笑 好了吗
Let's do it. Let's do it.
好了 开始吧
Saddle up. Rolling!
预备 开机
Action!
开始
It's my dog.
那是我的狗
My dog!
我的狗
And I will die if l do not have him back. Do you understand?!
我死也要把它要回来 明白了吗 我要把它弄回来
I will die if l do not have him back!
就算死了 我也要把它要回来
Cut.
停
Well, that was a bit much, Jack. You wanna take it down a notch?
你演得过火了 杰克 不要那么夸张 好吗低调一点
Or five?
低调一点 低调 明白低调吗
You know what? Just keep it going. Let me just go. I'll get it this time.
继续拍 这次我一定演得好的 好的 可以了
Rolling!
我可以了
Action!
开机
Where art thou, dog?
你在何处
Thy canine lover.
我心头的爱大
What's happening?
他在搞仕么
Where is your hot breath upon the nape of my neck?
你的气息令我深感怀念
We shall form a bond of brotherhood: man and beast.
我们俩个日夜相守 情同手足
You shall lick my face and I shall lick your snout.
你用舌头添我的脸 我用舌头添你的鼻子
Cut. Jack.
停 杰克
Guys, I'm not doing this on purpose, Il swear to you.
我发拆 我不是故意的 我也不想那样
Okay. All right.
好吧 那就再来一次
Rolling.
开始
Oh, my God. Where's my dog?
我的天啊 我的狗去哪儿了
Totally. l have a totally great dog.
我的狗是最好的
Jack. Jack. What are you doing?
杰克 你在干什么
This is where the dog has to decide between Darrin's ex and Darrin.
现在 小狗要选择戴伦或是前女友
Samantha wiggles her nose and the dog chooses Darrin.
珊曼莎 一扭鼻子 小狗就选择戴伦
Rolling!
开始
I know how we can solve this, Darrin. We'll let Satchel decide.
我有个点子 让狗狗自己选
That's a great idea.
这是一个好主意
-Come to Daddy, Satchel. -Look! Good boy.
来爸爸这儿 来 你看这个
-Come to Mommy. -Good boy.
来妈妈这几
-Satchel.... -Okay, Isabel, wiggle your nose.
乖狗狗 伊莎贝 扭鼻子
Satchel. Satchel. Come to Mommy.
到妈妈这几
-Satchel. Satchel. -Come on. Come on. Up!
来呀 跳上来 来呀
-Right here. Come to Daddy. -Come to Mommy, Satchel.
来妈妈这 来爸爸这儿 过来
I got it, Jack. I got it.
我有一个办法
Don't you dare go to Daddy. Come to Mommy!
别去找和爸爸 来找妈妈
-No, no, no. You love Daddy. -Come on, Satchel.
你最爱爸爸了 不是吗啊
-Come on.
快来呀 来呀
Satchel, come to Mommy.
快来妈妈这儿 来呀
-He's coming. He's coming. -He's just sitting there.
快过来 它一直坐着不动
Come on! Come on, boy!
快来呀
To Mommy, Satchel.
它来了 它来了
-Cut! -Jim, what's going on here?
停 它到底搞什么呀
Joey!
乔伊
If the dog runs to you again, try this.
它再跑去你那儿 你就念这名台词
Come to Daddy, Satchel.
来爸爸这儿 来
Satchel, come to Mommy.
狗狗 来妈妈这儿
Come on! Come on, Satchel.
来呀 狗狗 来爸爸这儿 来
-Come on, boy, please? -To Mommy.
快去呀 快去呀
Good girl.
狗狗 来爸爸这儿 来妈妈这几
Please, boy, come on! Jump, boy! Jump!
拜托你快跳吧
Thank God you didn't have a Great Dane.
幸好它不是大丹犬
Damn it!
可恶
Cut!
停
Darling, that was marvelous.
你演得太好了
But.... Watch out for that.
不过你要小心别被看穿了
Please don't say anything.
请你不要说出去
Calm down, you're not alone.
不是只有你
-I'm not? -No.
不是吗 当然了
-Are there others? -There are many others.
还有别人吗
Many actors, they develop tricks...
太多人了 演员都有自己的
.. twitches, really.
拿手好戏 不过
You don't want to become mannered.
二万别被定型了
-Oh, no, I don't. -No.
哦 我不会的
Thank you, Iris.
哦 谢谢你的忠告
Hello.
你好
Daddy, what--?
和爸爸
If it isn't my spell-casting magical daughter who gave up witchcraft.
这不是我那个下定决心 不再施魔法的女儿吗
You've had quite a day today, haven't you?
你今天表现得真不赖
l was provoked. I fell off the wagon. It was a one-time thing.
我是太生气了 才会破例的 下不为例
So you're not in love with him anymore?
你不再爱他了吗
I have never disliked a man more in my entire life...
我从来没这么讨厌过一个人
.. which proves that lam completely over him.
这证明找对他没成觉了
Not necessarily. In fact--
那可不一定 事实上
Besides, it was just a crush, which is an intense but superficial attraction...
我只是一开始被他吸引
.. that can easily be mistaken for something deeper. Now go away.
但那并不是真正的爱情 你快走吧 别在跟着我了
l have a crush on Endora.
我爱上安多拉了
What?!
什么
Daddy, where are you?
爸爸 你在哪儿呢
l said, l have a crush on Endora.
我说我爱上安多拉了
-Daddy! No. -So lovely.
那可不行 她好美哦
Her name is not Endora. It's Iris.
她不是安多拉 她叫艾莉丝
Iris. A spring flower.
艾莉丝 花一般的美人
You can't.
你不能追她
Now that I turned out to be so wrong about him, my job is all that I've got.
我看错杰克了 只剩这份工作了
-Please don't mess it up. -How could I do that?
你可不要再害我摘硬了 怎么会呢
You'll sleep with her, cheat on her...
等你追上她 一定又会把她甩掉
.. she'll go crazy and she'll take it out on me.
她一定会发疯似的拿我出气
I don't want you to get involved with Iris. 1 mean it.
知道吗 我不准你招车艾莉丝 和爸爸
You can't stop being a witch.
你也戒不掉魔法
I can too. You'll see.
我可以 你等着瞧
-Cannot. -Can too.
你办不到 我可以
-Just accept it. -Never.
接受事实吧 才不呢
Tell me about Bewitched.
请你谈一谈 神仙家庭
Some have said it's a crass attempt by the network to market nostalgia...
有人批评说这是炒冷饭
father than take a risk on new ideas.
一点都没有新的创意
This isn't the old Bewitched. It's been refocused,
这不是旧版的 神仙家庭 我们注入很多新的元素
Let's just say the only thing ! won't be doing is this:
我绝对不会来这一招的
So you leave the nose-wiggling to the witch.
只有女巫才会扭鼻子
But you do it so well,
可是你也很会扭耶
Well, l don't know about that. ! did coach her, though.
哦 对了 这一招是我教她的
Can we get a close-up on the nose?
给他的鼻子来个特写
I'd rather not.
那好吧
Which camera?
几号摄影机
Here? Okay.
好吧
Shall we discuss...
让咱们谈一谈
. dare we discuss, Last Year in Katmandu?
去年的 西藏大疯狂
Hi, Nina.
你好 路 妮娜 对
Yes! Yes, l am watching him.
对 我正在看
What's a dick?
王八蛋是什么
No one ever sets out to make a bad movie.
没有人会故意拍一部破片
What does that have to do with how obnoxious he is being?
这跟他是大坏蛋有什么关系
Some movies are career-enders.
有些破片会毁了一个演员
Right. Right, we need a plan.
没错 我们得想办法
What went wrong?
那部片出了什么错呢
You know, I hate to point fingers...
我并不想怪罪任何人
..but I'm gonna blame the wardrobe department.
不过那是服装部门的错
The wardrobe department?
服装部门
! think it got in the way.
服装毁了整部戏
Maybe I should quit.
也许我该辞职了
Honey, you can't quit.
亲爱的 你不能辞职不干
Why not? Isn't that what people do?
为什么不能 大家都这么做
He has to quit, not you.
该走的应该是他 不是你
Yeah, like that's ever gonna happen.
没错 不过他死都不会走的
We have to make him quit.
那就要他逼走
If we get naked pictures of him and pictures of farm animals...
只要我们能和弄到他的裸照
....1 could just Photoshop them.
就能用计算机合成摘出丑闻来
That's an excellent idea.
真是个好主意
No, no, no. Wait. Calm down. Calm down.
等等 不行咬 冷静点
No, no, no, this not what I wanted. I wanted something normal.
冷静点 我只想过平凡的生活
What should I do?
我该怎么办
Oh, my.
哦 讨厌
What a mess.
我全身都弄得脏兮兮的
Your Aunt Clara used to be able to make a clean landing.
哦 你克莉阿姨以前都能 成功降落的这次怎么了
Aunt Clara?
克莉阿姨
Oh, Aunt Clara.
哦 克莉阿姨
Oh, thank goodness you're here.
哦
lam in the middle of a total, total crisis at work. I'm quitting.
你来了 真是谢天谢地 我正好遇到了工作危机
You mustn't quit. The show must go on.
我要辞职了 你不能辞职 戏要演下去
Isabel, are you all right?
伊莎贝 你没事吧
Oh, my friends-- I have friends-- They don't know we're witches.
我的朋友 她不知道我们是女巫
Mum's the word.
千万不能说 我会守口如瓶的
You know, there was an Aunt Clara on the original Bewitched.
神仙家庭 也有克莉阿姨
What a coincidence!
那真巧
She was a witch.
她是个女巫
So aml.
我也是呀 她老是出错
She was always screwing up.
而且不停的出错
-Really? -l have made up my mind.
真的吗 我下定决心了
lam quitting tomorrow and I'll do something else, like sailing...
我决定明天就去辞职 去当个水手什么的
..or polishing fruit.
或者去当个果农
It's too bad you're not a witch, you could put a hex on Jack.
你真的是女巫 就能对杰克施魔法
Oh, I can. I certainly can.
我当然可以喝 当然可以
Who is Jack?
杰克是谁呀
The reason I'm quitting.
我辞职的原因
Well, why not put a hex on him.
你为什么不对他施法
Because I'm giving it up.
因为我戒掉魔法了
-Just a little one. -Aunt Clara.
再破一次 克莉阿姨
Just to get him to behave.
只是让他乖一点
I'll do it.
让我来施魔法
And then I can keep my job. Which would help my self-esteem.
只要我保住工作 我就会有自信的
You know, there's only one problem with a hex.
我想提醒你
There's no such thing as magic.
世上没有魔咒这种东西
So...
那 恩
.. what's your idea, Little Miss Doubtful?
那你有什么好点子吗
-Well, l have a Taser. -Nina.
我有一个电击棒 妮娜
l think we should Taser him and throw him into the shark tank at SeaWorld.
我们把他击昏 然后把他丢进效鱼池
No. You think we should do a hex.
不 你觉得应该对他下广咒吗
Il think we should do a hex.
我觉得应该对他下魔贺
Pinch of jasmine.
一点茉莉花
Wolfbane.
一点乌头草
Grapefruit pith.
柚子局
I feel so alive.
我觉得好兴奋哦
I feel like one of those people I'd make fun of.
我好像已经感觉到魔贺的威力
I feel like I believe in unicorns.
我相信有独角兽
Did I put in the wolfbane? I can't remember.
我放了乌头草了 我不记得了
-Aunt Clara. -Thank you, darling. Thank you.
克莉阿姨 谢谢
Oh, well.
好吧
Isabel.
伊莎贝
Bonana-fana fo-fel
你是我的宝贝
Fee-fy-fo-fel
你是我宝贝
Isabel
宝贝我的宝贝
"The Name Game"!
伊莎贝
-Oh, boy. -Good morning.
让我们结婚吧 哇 早上好
Randall, take that stupid sign off that machine.
快把那个家伙拿开
Free cappuccinos for everyone.
大家都有免费咖啡喝 我请客 我太高兴了
-How we doing? Anyone seen Isabel? -No, why?
你们看到伊莎贝了吗 没看 怎么了
Because I miss her.
我好想她哦
-Listen, Jack. -Yes?
听好了 杰克 什么事
We got the test scores from the pilot...
试片的结果已经出来了 调查结果
How did Isabel do? Ninety-nine percent in the top box!
伊莎贝得了9 9分
Why didn't you tell me? This is great news.
干嘛不早点告诉我呀 这真是个好消息 你没事吧
Of course she got a 99 percent. Because she's dynamite.
当然了 好消息 因为她太棒了
Absolute dynamite.
真的很棒啊
High-fives all the way around.
大家一起击党庆祝吧
But, Jack, there is a problem. Your scores...
问题是你的分数
Thirty-two percent. That's better than zero, huh?
3 2分 总比鸭蛋好吧 这是有建设性的批评
You know what? That's constructive criticism.
你看连那只小狗
The dog scored higher than me. He's a cute dog.
都比我受欢迎 它真是可爱的小狗啊
What do the comment cards say?
我得到什么评语了
Oh, they don't really...
其实并不是
But a good tool. Like a Jacksaw!
不过你是个好花瓶 我不介意 好花瓶
You know what? Who cares? This just means we got hard work to do, okay?
这代表我还有进步的空间吗 因为我
Hey, I never said I was perfect. The important thing is Isabel.
不可能是完美的 重点是伊莎贝
-lsabel. -Yeah, no question.
伊莎贝 毫无疑问
-Agreed? -Totally on board.
大家同意吗
Good morning, everyone.
各位早上好
There she is!
她来了
Is it just my imagination, or is the room actually brighter with her here?
是我眼花 还是什么了 她全身发光
Look at this bundle of miraculous talent.
她真是仙女下凡呀 我要给她满分
Forget 99, I give her 100! 100!
一百分 一百分啊 一百分
Rehearsing!
开始排练
"Interior, apartment, day.
日戏 内景 公寓
Samantha and Darrin are sitting in their overcrowded apartment."
珊曼莎和戴伦坐在家
Darrin, I think we should buy a house and I found one that I love.
我看中一间房子 应该买下来
You nailed that!
你演得太棒了
I'm about to have a heart attack. Isn't she great?
我关点就心脏病发作 她棒不棒啊
And now I kiss her, because she's in love with our new house.
我真的很想亲你 因为她很爱新家呀
Oh, you can't kiss me. I'm not in this scene.
你不能亲我 这场戏没有我
-You're not in the scene? -No.
这场戏没有你 没有
No, no, no. She isn't in the scene? This isn't happening! What?!
不行 不行 每么可以这样呢
She has to be in every scene! Okay?
每场戏都要有她 每场戏都要有她 可以吗
Rewrite! Go! Rewrite.
写 重写剧本 快去 重写剧本 快去 快去重写 快
Everyone, Isabel needs a joke.
各位 我觉得伊莎贝需要一个笑话
I would love a joke.
我很想说个笑话
One joke, coming up.
笑话马上来
Oh, and then I kiss her because she's so funny.
她真的很可爱 我好想要亲亲她
And a job. She needs a job.
还有工作 她也需要一份工作
Yes! Yes! Make this woman the CEO of a multinational corporation.
对 对 她是一家跨国公司的执行长
-Good idea, Jack. -No. Great idea.
她是一家跨国公司的执行长 对 没错 好主意
And then I kiss her because she's so powerful.
这主意绝了 她是女强人 所以我又要亲她了
It's too much, what happened?
这有点过火 出了什么问题了
Aunt Clara. Aunt Clara?
克莉阿姨 克莉阿姨
Please pick up the phone, something terrible is happening.
快接电话呀”发生大事情了
Something terrible is happening.
真是件大事情
I know, I know. It wasn't supposed to, and--
我知道 我知道 真不应该这样 真的不该这样
You should never, ever get involved with an actor.
你不应该跟同台演员交往
I'm not involved with him, I don't think.
我没有跟他交往 我没有 没有
-Witch's honor? -What?
女巫的保证 什么
I'm just being Endora.
我在演安多拉吗
Isabel, actors look normal, sometimes better than normal.
演员看起来很漂亮很聪明
But deep down, there is no deep down.
可是他们全都是草包 草包 懂吗
l thought you were safe. He loathed you.
我以为你能逃过他的魔掌 他原来不是讨厌你吗
What on earth happened?
怎么了
A little witchcraft, l suspect.
我怀疑她用了点魔法
Even though we weren't going to do it, were we, darling?
虽然你答应不用了 对吧
I'm Nigel Bigelow, I'm Isabel's father. How do you do?
我是伊莎贝的老爸奈吉 你好
Daddy, we talked about this, remember?
哦 爸爸 我敬告过你 记得吗
-l'm.... -l know who you are.
我是 我早已经久仰大名了
I've seen everything you've ever done.
我看过你演的每一部剧
Lysistrata in Florence, Blithe Spirit in New York.
《利西尉姐》《欢乐精灵》 和爸爸
-Daddy! -But your Endora is a marvel.
你把安多拉演得活灵活现了
It comes so easily, really.
其实演起来很容易 是呀
Oh, yes, because I am a witch.
因为我真的是一个女巫
-Oh, really? -Oh, yes.
真的吗 真的
I put out all the lights in Leicester Square just by walking past.
纽约大停电就是我的杰作
Oh, tell me more. Tell me everything.
哦 是吗 快说来听听
-Oh, please come in. -Charmed.
请进来吧 我们 好好聊聊吧 那太好了
This is just.... What--?
这下惨了 怎么办
Isabel!
伊莎贝
Hey! Isabel! Isabel!
嘿 伊莎贝 伊莎贝
Hi! Listen, maybe we could go to dinner tonight. God, I'm so nervous.
嘿 嗨 也许咱们今晚可以一起吃饭
- don't think so, I have to get home. -We won't make it a date.
天啊 我好紧张 不行 我得回家 我要回家
I'll just happen to stop by and ask if you're hungry.
i 这不算约会 我会正好经过你家看你俄不饿 好
-No. -Yes! That's a yes!
不行 不行 好咬 你说好了
-No! -I'll be by at great.
不好 峨 太好了
I mean, I'll be by at 8.
我八点准时到你家
Stop by if you need anything. I'm right here. Okay.
找会到你家找你
Aunt Clara!
克莉阿姨
Undo it! Undo it! You overdid it! Undo it!
你下的魔法太强了
-Oh, dear. -Aunt Clara!
快解除 快解除 快除掉吧 哦 天啊 快呀
I'm not too sure how to undo it. Undoing it's not the same as doing it.
我不会解除的 这跟施法不一样 不一样
He wants to have dinner. This isn't what I wanted.
他要请我吃饭 这可不行v
Lorna Doone?
吃饼干吗
No!
不要
Darling, I'm sure you can undo the hex if you really want to.
我想你一定有办法自己解除魔法
I'm expected in Japan.
我得赶去日本了
That certainly didn't work, did it?
我又出错了
Aunt Clara?
克莉阿姨
Aunt Clara, come back here right now.
克莉阿姨 快回来
He's gonna be here any minute. Aunt Clara!
你快回来 他马上就到了
But that doesn't matter, because I'm not going out with him.
不管怎么样我都不会跟他约会的
No, no, I'm not. I'm not!
不 我不能去 不能去
Oh, I'd better--
我最好是
Oh, who cares what I look like.
谁在乎我穿什么呀
I'm just gonna undo the hex.
找要解除魔法
I'm not even gonna bother dressing up.
我要解除魔法 干嘛还要打扮呢
I'm just gonna open the door, undo it and slam the door in his face!
哦 我要开门 解除魔法 然后让他吃闭门效
Hey. I just happened to be in the neighborhood with these roses...
解除魔法 快 嘿 我正好带了一束玫瑰花
..and a Cat Stevens CD...
一张CD
..and this bracelet...
和一条手链
..and I thought I'd stop by.
我经过这里 就想来找你
-You're sweating. -Like a pig.
你在流汗 汗流污背
Oh, how divine.
哦 好美哦
You look stunning.
你才美呢
No! Ravishing.
不 你是仙女下凡
You look "stunnishing.”
你比仙女还美
Is this your purse?
这是你的皮包
You're not too cold, are you?
你觉得冷吗
-No. -You're not too warm?
不冷 那热吗
Okay.
很好
-Are we going somewhere? -Dinner.
我们要去哪里 吃饭了呀
Here. Here you go.
来吧 走
l wanna know everything.
我想知道你的一切
You talk, okay? I'm just gonna listen.
你尽管说 好吗 我听你说
Shed your radiance and I'll just soak it up like a plant.
我会沐浴在你的光环之中
Start in kindergarten.
你就从幼儿园说起吧
I didn't go to kindergarten. l was homeschooled.
我没有上过幼儿园 我是在家自学的
You were homeschooled? So was I.
真的吗 我也是耶
How amazing. That's freaky.
这未免太巧了吧
I'm getting chills.
我都起鸡皮疙将了
Yeah, that is kind of amazing.
卫 是的是很挺巧的
My parents were hippies. Were yours?
我父母是嬉皮士 你的呢
-No. -That's so weird!
都不是 太夸张了
My parents were hippies, and yours weren't. What are the odds?
你爸妈怎么这么巧不是嬉皮士呢
But we did have incense and candles.
我们家烧很多香和晴烛
-So did we. -You did?
我们家也是耶 真的吗
To this day, incense makes me puke.
我闻到烧香的味道都会吐
Yes, me too!
对 我也是
-Amazing! -Wow.
好巧哦
I brought duck.
哇 我带了烤鸭
Il love duck.
哦 我最爱吃烤鸭了
So do I. How amazing is that?
我也是 怎么这么巧 啊太巧了
Well, most people love duck.
大部份人都爱吃烤鸭
You know what? No, they don't.
其实并没有带烤鸭
Wait. l wrote you a song.
等会儿 我为你写了一首歌
No one's ever written me a song.
没人为我写过歌
Well, I did.
可我就写了 你听上听
Hey, pretty lady
漂亮的女孩
Come back here with my heart
你打动了我的心
Are you a dream made real?
你实现了我的梦
My soul, you have healed
你安抚了我受创的心灵
Make me a better man
让我成为更好的男人
! wanna set up residence
我想要和你携手共同
In your promised land
打造美好家园
Okay, and this is the power ballad guitar solo.
接下来 是狂劲的电吉他独奏
Now you sing the chorus.
你一起来唱
Promised land
打造美好家园
Drum solo.
对 鼓手独奏
Promised land!
打造美好家圆
Leg kick.
踢服
Okay, I'm gonna break the guitar.
我要摔断吉他了
Promised land!
打造美好家园
We're about to kiss, aren't we?
我们要亲嘴了 对吧
l thought so, but thanks for ruining the moment, Miss Narrator.
是啊 多谢你现在的旁白谢谢
Oh, my ruby jewel.
哦 我的珍珠宝石
-What? -My chocolate-covered strawberry.
什么 我的草莓巧克力
I wanna bask in our love...
我要沉浸在我俩的爱情里
. like a house cat lying in the sun.
就像一只猫咪沐浴在阳光下
Jack, Jack, Jack. Stop. Stop. I forgot.
峨不 杰克 杰克 杰克不行
Oh, I let myself forget.
停一下 停一下 对不起
It was so nice, I couldn't help myself, and....
我让自己太放纵了 这种感觉很棒
Oh, Jack!
我很享受”但是 杰克 不行
This is sad. This is.... No.
对不起
Let's make love in a hot-air balloon.
让我们在热气球上欢乐
Let's make love in a candy factory.
让我们在糖果工厂亲吻 不 不
Let's make love in a petting zoo.
让我们在可爱动物园跳舞 让我们来吧
I have to undo this, I do.
我必须解除这种爱情魔法
Let's make love at SeaWorld, on the back of a killer whale.
必须解除 让我们在 海洋公园里翻云覆雨
Because it doesn't mean anything unless it's real.
如果不是来真的那就不算数
What witches wish No mortal needs
女巫的魔法 凡人的诅咒
Let time repent And unsow its seeds
让时光倒流 让一切还原
And now, I speak the ancient word of redemption and regret:
我将说出追悔的古老语言 倒带
So you leave the nose-wiggling to the witch.
谢谢 谢谢 只有女巫才会扭鼻子
-But you do it so well. -1 did coach her, though.
可是你也很会扭耶 这一招是我教她的
Can we get a close-up on the nose?
给他的鼻子来个特写
I'd rather not.
不要除
Which camera?
那好吧 几号摄影机
Hello, Nina.
你好 妮娜
I just knew it was you, that's all.
我猜应该是你
Yes, he is. He is a giant male reproductive organ.
是的 没错 是个百分之百的大坏蛋
We don't need a plan, I already know what I'm gonna do.
不用了 我知道该怎么做
I'm gonna speak to him about his behavior.
我要直接跟他摊牌
I'm gonna talk to him sensibly and directly, and I know he will change.
我要理性地和他沟通 他一定会改过自新
You'll see. Bye.
你等着瞧吧 拜拜
Butt out, Samantha, I know what I'm doing.
别插手 我自己来
I mean it.
我是说真的
Bonana-fana fo-fack
我爱杰克 他最棱
Fee-fi-bo-back
全世界他最棒 杰克
Guys, make me 20 cappuccinos. Bring me the best one.
蔡我者 2 0 杯卡布其诺 把最好喝的那杯给我
The test scores are in.
试片的调查结果已经出炉了
How'd I do? Ninety? Hundred? One-twenty.
我得了多少分 啊 多少分90 120
-One-forty! -Good ballpark.
不 140 不
What did it say? I got it. I got it right here.
这到底是多少 我自己看吧
Thirty-two.
32分
I got a 32?
我得32分
ls that for real?
真的还是假的
The dog scored higher than I did.
连小狗的分数都比我高啊
Well, it's not you, Jack, it's Darrin.
不是你杰克是戴伦
"That Jack Wyatt is a real tool. We hate him.
杰克太差了我们讨厌他
We mean the actor, not the character."
是讨厌他的本人不是他的角色
Get a grip.
振作点
Hug me.
让我抱抱
I'm gonna be doing dinner theater in Boca Raton.
我会沦为工地秀主持人
They hate the show, the whole show.
他们讨厌整出电视剧
They hate everyone on it.
他们讨厌每个角色
-Yeah, everybody. -They did. Yep.
每个人都很惨 没错
Isabel must've gotten savaged.
伊莎贝一定被批评得体无完肤吧
She got a 997!
她得了99分
Ninety-nine? Is this for real?
99分 真的假的啊
Is that a joke?
这是开玩笑吗
She didn't say anything!
她只是个大花瓶
How is it that someone who doesn't say anything...
她怎么会比 男主角的分数还要高呢
..scores higher than someone who had all the lines?
嗪 我的天哪
Did anyone anticipate this as a possibility?
哦 不可能的怎么会有这种结果呢
Hindsight's 20(20.
这很难预料的
-Good morning, everyone. -And they think I'm a tool?!
各位早上好 他们说我太差了
l haven't been called a tool since Il was 15!
高中以后就没人说过我差了
Thank you, guys! Thank you!
谢谢大家了哦 谢谢了
You know what? No one ever liked Darrin! No one!
以前就没有人喜欢戴伦 没有人
Why did we ever think that was gonna change?
现在怎么会有人改变呢
Il have something to say.
我有话要说
This is unbelievable! A 32?
我真不敢相信 32分 真的假的
That's for real? A three in front of a two?
3在2的前面 哦 天啊
Oh, my God!
怎么可能呢
Wait, l have something to say.
等等 我有话要说
A 32 and she got 997!
我得32分 她得99分
Were they high?!
我说那些观众
Were the people in the test group high?
他们是不是吃错药了
Did we drug test them?
他们没有接受药检吗
Were they just sitting in the studio, smoking crack, saying:
八成是吃错药了 他们是不是吃了摇头丸
"Let's give her a 99 and him a 32. By the way, I'm high on crack"?!
给她99分 给我32分 哦 天啊 我实在是倒性透了
I have something to say!
听着我有话要说
What?!
什么
You're a jerk.
你是个大混蛋
What did you just say?
你说什么
l said, you're a jerk!
我说你是个大混蛋
Everything is about you.
你只想到你自己你
You are selfish. And you are self-centered.
你是个自私自利的自大狂 你骗我你说你需要我
And you lied to me, you said you needed me. You don't need anyone!
你根本就不需要我是个大混蛋
Listen, sweetie, why don't you go to your trailer and take a Midol?
请你到你们的休息 车上吃一颗镇静剂吧
Hey! You be quiet, or I'll give you a tail!
嘿 给我闭嘴 不然我让你长尾巴
-Just calm down. -You sit down!
你冷静点 你给我坐下
Sit down!
坐下
This show is supposed to be about a marriage.
这出电视剧讲的是一对夫妻
Areal marriage, with real problems, like what color to paint the kitchen...
真正的婚姻 真实的问题 像是厨房要漆什么颜色
..or, L don't know, other problems, l can't even think of them now.
我一时也想不出什么别的问题
But the only problems you care about are your own!
不过你只想到你自己的问题
No wonder the audience doesn't like this show!
怪不得观众不喜欢这出电视剧
A witch marries a mortal.
女巫嫁给凡人
Who in their right mind would want to marry you?
只有疯子才会嫁给你这种人
-Hey! -Excuse me. That's it. You're fired.
你说够了吗 你被开除了
Doesn't matter. I quit!
无所谓 我不干了
Yeah! So...
没错 好吧
.. you better call my agent.
打电话给我的经纪人
You don't have an agent.
你没有经纪人
Then call my cable man!
那就麻烦你打给我吧
Sorry. So...
对不起
You all right?
你没事吧
No one's talked to me like that in 20 years.
二十年来没人这样痛骂过我
Once a week a woman talks to me like that.
每星期都有女人吕我
She just stripped me bare and stuck the knife in.
她的话就像一把刀刺进我心中
Let's go to The Peninsula and get some oysters.
我们去半岛酒店吃生峡吧
You know what I think?
你知道吗 嘿 她需要更多戏份
-Hey. The woman needs a part. -I'm sorry?
什么
I mean, if you got Sammy Sosa, you don't bench him.
你不会让麦克尔乔丹坐冷板癸吧
If you got Gorbachev in the ballet, you let him dance the big number.
芭蕾舞团有戈尔巴乔夫 总不能让他跑龙套吧
I don't think Gorbachev was a dancer.
戈尔巴乔夫不是跳舞的
Yes, he was, Richie, he absolutely was. Look it up.
他当然是 你自己去查查看吧
Isabel! Hey!
伊莎贝
Wait, wait, wait, don't go!
等等 等等 别走
Please don't go. Please don't go. That was incredible.
你别走 别走 你刚才说的很对
-What? -Just now. That.
什么“就是你刚才说的话呀
I mean, you yelled at me. You were up-front, and honest...
你对我大吼大叫 说出实话
..and you called me out on all my crap.
把我的缺点全都说了出来
It was just great.
你真是了不起
Oh, God, I'm hyperventilating.
你把我驾得狗血淋头啊 啊 天啊
I've never done anything like this.
我从来没这么做过 现在
It was very hard, but secretly quite thrilling.
心里有点难受 不过也很痛快
Even my ex-wife, she never yelled. She just locked me out.
我前妻 她就只会把我锁在门外
In my family, we usually just disappear.
但我的家人通常都会消失不见
No, no, don't disappear, Isabel. One more show.
不要消失 别跟我说 你等等伊莎贝 再拍一些
-I don't think so. -No, one more taping. Please?
再拍一集 求求你 好吗
It's just that I'm feeling that-- I'm feeling like maybe....
不行 我觉得 我觉得 只是 很对不起啊
-I'm sorry. -What'd you say?
伊莎贝 对不起 你说什么
I'm sorry for how I've been. I'm sorry.
我为我的行为向你道次
You're sweating again.
你又在流汗了
I know, just...
我知道
I just-- Look, one more.
请你再拍一集
I love it when you sweat.
我喜欢看你流汗
One more! Just one more.
再给我一次机会吧 好吗
And the second I'm being a jerk, you can yell, "Hey! He's being a jerk!"
如果 我在摆什么臭架子的话 你就大声骂我 杰克是个大混蛋
And we'll shut the whole thing down, I promise.
然后我们就马上停止录像
We'll burn down the sets...
把布景给烧掉
..and sell the costumes, and give the money to little children.
再把戏服卖掉 把钱捐给孤儿院
I mean, that's one possible scenario.
我是说真的伊莎贝
You want me to say "He's being a jerk"?
你要我说 杰克是个混蛋
Yeah. Or you can yell, 1 mean...
对 对 大声叫也行
He's being a jerk!
杰克是个大混蛋
Yes.
很好
I can't just walk back in there now.
我没有脸再走回去了
Once you show up on a golf cart, believe me, all is forgiven.
你只要坐高尔夫球车回去 想信我他们就会欢迎你的
I've done it a lot of times.
这种事我干过很多次了
But I was fired. Oh, no. That's right, I quit.
我被开除 不 我是自己不干的
Yeah. Here, let me carry your plant.
没错 我帮你拿东西 来
Honey, your mother's here.
老婆 你妈妈来了
Are you two getting along?
你们俩个还好吗
Not exactly.
不太好
-Like this? -You're doing great.
是这样吗
Really, really great. One more time.
很好 来再试一次 来
So it says here that marriage can lead to a loss of passion.
大家都说婚姻是爱情的坟墓
It's true. feel empty and bored already.
没错 我的心 早就已经死了
-Oh, great. It's you. -Mother!
哦 我的天啊 又是你呀
Il see you two are actually getting along?
妈妈 你们小俩口挺恩爱的嘛
Endora, you rancid fruit bag, get out of my room.
安多拉 你给我出去 离开我的房间 快
-Darrin! -And my daughter is happy?
戴伦 我女儿好像很幸福
That is the cruelest twist of all.
这真是让人想像不到呀
lam happy, Darrin. Real, honest, no-spells happy.
我很幸福 戴伦 是真的 没用魔法哦
And cut!
停
Actors, cut.
俩位 够了 停
Really, cut now.
我喊停了
You were great today. Just absolutely amazing.
你今天演
I don't think I've ever had so much fun.
我从来没有玩得这么开心过
Acting is fun.
玩的很开心
That is a profoundly true thing.
演戏本来就很好玩 这是二真万确的
Would you like a water chestnut?
你想吃点水果吗
I'd love a water chestnut.
好啊 我非常喜欢吃水果
I'm gonna teach you everything I know...
我要把我全身的本领都教给你
.. Starting with...
先从
..the eye thing.
翻白眼开始
The famous crazy-eye thing of mine.
我举世闻名的翻白眼演技
Okay?
看好了哦
This almost won me a Golden Globe.
这一招差点让我赢得金球奖
Almost.
只差一点
-ls that it? -That's good.
这样吗 是 很好
Oh, that's even better.
这样更好
This is the "I just realized things are worse than they seem" thing.
这是发现情况不钞的表情 知道吗
Also known as "the Yikes Take."
也被称为 哎呀演技
Yikes!
哟 哎呀
Wow.
哇
-That was terrible. -It's okay.
我好差
-No, I was terrible. - don't think mine was good, either.
还好哎 我太差了 不 我演得也不怎么样
That's it. I'm out of tricks.
没了 我就那么几招了
-What about the funny walk you do? -The funny walk?
你的搞笑脚步呢 搞笑脚步
-You don't wanna see the walk. -l do.
你不会想看的图 我想看
Funny walk is embarrassing.
那一招很丢脸的
I'd like to see it.
我想看 真的
Yeah?
唱
Okay. Let's go to our place.
好吧 不如到我们家
Magic hour.
魔幻时刻
-ls that it? -That's great.
是这样吗 很棒
It's much harder than it looks.
这比看起来更难 是的
Five, six, seven, eight.
五六七八
-Move back! -Hey!
退后一点 退后
Something magical happened all by itself.
赴露 爱情魔法自然生效了
Table read in 10 minutes!
十分钟后排演
Okay, close it up!
把门关起来
-Good morning, everyone. -Morning, Jack.
大家早上好 早上好 杰克
Look, Jack, I just need to talk to you about a couple of these things.
杰克 我得跟你谈件事
Number one, we're thinking about moving...
我在重新考虑 厨房那场戏
.. the whole kitchen scene. Just-- It's such--
你看那场戏 那场戏必须要改
It's a funny scene.
那场戏很好笑
It's really funny. We'd like to get it in a little earlier.
对 所以我才想要放在前面
So probably what we're gonna do is switch it with the office.
跟办公室那场戏对调 你看
But we're gonna drop that to a little later on in the show.
不过后来会再出现一次
Dude. Dudes, are you watching Jack throw the vibe to Isabel right now?
我不是告诉过你吗 你们快看 杰克在对伊莎贝放电呢
How are you?
你好吗
I'm great.
我棒极了
That's for you.
你的剧本
Thank you.
谢谢
-Call me. -That's fantastic.
打给我
Stop.
实在太好了
Fine.
够了晓
Yeah. I mean, I can find something for him.
好吧 我可以蔡他安排点戏份
I'll put him in a little part with maybe no lines or anything like that.
也许是没有台词的戏份
What is going on between you and Jack?
伊莎贝 你是不是跟杰克好上了
Nothing is going on.
没有呀
We had a date and we kissed...
我们约会 亲吻
..and now we just wanna spend all of our time together.
随时随地都想在一起
That is the very definition of something going on.
伊莎贝 这就代表你们俩个好上了
And you know what? I didn't use any tricks. l am trick-free.
我并没有用魔法 完全出于自然
Oh, my God, it's her.
顺其自然的 哦 天啊
l saw a picture of her in InStyle when she was the fashion "don't."
我在时尚杂志看过她的恶心照片 你看就是她 她走过来了
Excuse me. I'm looking for Jack.
她走过来了 对不起 我找杰克
You must be Samantha.
你一定是珊曼莎
You look just like the old one.
你跟以前那位演员好像蛾
Thank you so much.
哦 多谢夸奖
Oh, excuse me.
妮娜 哦 失陪了
Love the nose.
你扭鼻子的那一招很厉害
Good work.
真是不错
There he is. There's my guy.
他来了 我老公
I've missed him so much.
我好想他哦
Let's just say the "Do Not Disturb" sign will be on the doorknob tonight.
今晚我们房门会挂上 请勿打扰 的门牌
-Oh, my God! -Oh, God!
典 天啊 天啊
Help me lift it. Help me lift it. Slowly, slowly, slowly.
帮有我抬起来快点 慢慢来
That was a little harsh.
那好像有点过份
I've missed him so much.
今天
Let's just say the "Do Not Disturb" sign will be on the doorknob tonight.
晚上我们房门会挂上 请勿打扰 的门牌
-Sheila. -Hi, baby.
席拉 路 老公
What are you doing here?
你跑来这干嘛
You want my car? My grandmother's brooch.
你要我的车吗 我的传家之宝
Oh! You want more money.
哦 你要更多的钱 叮叮
Ding-ding-ding! Correct answer.
答对了
No.
不
-l want you back. -What about Captain Underpants?
我要你回到我身边 那你的内衣猛男呢
I'm through with him. Il love you, Jack.
我跟他完蛋了 我爱你 杰克
Oh, wait, wait, I get it. You heard that the show's getting picked up.
哦 我明白了 你听说电视剧要播出
I heard it's gonna be a hit.
我听说一定会大受欢迎的
But so what?
不过又怎样
I want you. I want my husband.
我只要你 我的老公
You know, a week ago I would've fallen for that.
一星期以前我会被你骗倒 可现在
But now there's someone else.
我找到另一个女人了
Someone who's incapable of guile.
一个永远不会鹿诈我的女人
What's guile?
诈是什么意思
I'm not gonna do it.
我不能这么做
I think it means tricks.
意思就是坎骗
-l love you, baby. -No, I'm not.
我爱你 亲爱的 我不能
Maybe I will.
也许可以
-What the heck is going on?! -Joey.
乔伊 到底是怎么回事
This place is spooked. I quit.
这地方闲鬼 我不干了 不干了
Joey. Joey, come back here.
乔伊 给我回来
Get me a mirror! Jack!
回来 给我一面镜子
-Jack! -Are you okay?
杰克 你还好吧
Am I okay?!
我好不好
And one more time.
再来一次
I'm fine. And I'm signing the divorce papers right now.
我很好 我现在就跟你签离婚协议书
You are?
真的吗
Maybe two.
也许来两次
And I'm moving out of the house this afternoon.
我今天下午就搬出去 再也不回来了
Where are you going?
你要去哪儿
-Where is it? -Iceland.
那在哪里”冰岛
I love ice.
我最爱冰了
Goodbye, everyone! I'm off to Reykjavik!
再见了各位
Oh, my God.
我要去冰岛 哦 天啊
Everyone, did you just see that?
你们看到没有
She's gonna sign the papers! This is incredible.
她要签离婚协议书耶真不可思议
-lsabel. -Party at my house!
她要签离婚协议书耶 真不可思议
You're out of control.
你失控了
Every time I think I have things nailed down, I just lose it.
每次我想戒掉的时候 就偏偏要破戒
Oh, don't be so hard on yourself. It's gonna be okay.
哦 别这么自责 不会有事的
Oh, whoa. Who is that?
哦 那人是谁呀
No, Maria. No.
玛莉亚 别招车他
Too late.
太迟了
Second of all, like--
站这
Everyone, can I have your attention, please? I just wanna say a few words.
谢谢 请大家听好 我要说几句话
Randall, can we deal with this? Thank you.
兰道 帮帮忙 谢谢
Where do I start? What a night. Is everyone having fun? Yeah?
好棒的派对 对 大家开心吗 开心 开心
Great. I'm so grateful for so many things tonight.
那就好 我要说的是 有好多事 要感谢大家 尤其是这出电视剧
The show, all of you amazing and talented people...
你们都这么有才华
..and especially Isabel.
尤其是伊莎贝
To a woman who'd never trick me into thinking...
她永远都不会对我隐瞒
..she was something she wasn't.
真实的自己
From now on, everyone tells the truth. Okay?
从现在起大家都要说实话 好吗
Except if 1 don't look good, say I do anyway.
除了我不帅也要说我帅之外
Isabel, you are a beautiful person.
伊莎贝 你真是个完美女人
And that's the truth.
这是我的肺腑之言 干杯
Have a great time.
大家玩得开心点
Cheers.
干杯
Don't break anything, okay?
别打破任何东西
-We won't, Jack. -Thank you.
不会图 谢谢 谢谢
l hope that touching speech...
我想不会因为他那番话
.. hasn't made you think that you should tell the truth.
你就要坦白一切吧
-I'm going to. -Oh, don't be silly.
我要跟他说 别傻了
And he's gonna accept me. He's got to. You can't live with a secret like that.
他会接受我的 我不能眶着他 和葡区
Of course you can. For thousands of years.
你当然行 几千年来都是这样
Don't do it. Big mistake. Won't work.
别告诉他 别犯这种大错误
Well, hello there. Now, don't tell me....
你好 请问这是椰子虾吗
Coconut shrimps.
啊
Oh, yes. Would you like one?
哦 对 你要来一只吗
Yes. Thank you.
是的 谢谢
Do you know, you're quite fetching.
你知道吗 你真的很美
And I'm Nigel Bigelow.
我是奈吉毕格罗
Yes. I will sleep with you because l have a thing for father figures.
我有恋父情结 我想跟你上床
Well, that's great, then.
卫 太好了
But in the morning, I will not get 90 percent of your jokes...
不过我听不懂你讲的古董笑话
..and I'll go on and on about opening an aerobics center in Agoura.
我也许会继续梦想开一问健身房
Are you looking for me?
你在找我吗
Missing you, actually.
其实我很想你
-How strange. -Not really.
真奇怪 一点也不
I'm just gonna say it like it's a completely matter-of-fact thing.
杰克 我要跟你说一件事
-Guess what. -What?
你猜猜是什么事 是什么
I'm a witch.
我是一个女巫
-Guess what. -What?
那又怎样 怎样
I'm a Clippers fan.
我是快艇队球迷
Yeah, it's not like it's a big deal.
对 这是没有什么大不了的
I'm not a bad witch, and we're getting it out there and telling the truth, right?
我又不是什么坏巫婆 而且我们要互相坦白 对吗
Right. And I'm not just a fan.
对 其实我不是他们的球迷
I made the mistake of buying courtside seats.
只是有一次买错了门票而已
No, no, no, really. Jack. Jack, l am. I, Isabel Bigelow, I'm a witch.
不不 我是说真的 杰克 我真的是女巫 女巫你懂
Okay, great. So you're a witch.
好吧 你是个女巫 好吗
Come on, let's make out in the hall closet.
来吧 我们到衣橱里面亲热亲热
-Jack. -Okay, okay, I'll play along.
杰克 来吧
Like it's an improv. Prove it.
我就陪你演下去 证明给我看
So I just said, "Listen, you guys, l believe Cher has another hit in her."
我是说雪儿还会拍一部卖座的影片
-Really? -Yeah.
真的吗 真的
Not a trick.
这不是魔术
Whoa! How'd you do that?
喔 你是怎么做到的
To the most powerful witch ever.
敬世界上法力最强大的女巫
Can you make an umbrella appear in this drink?
你能变出一把小雨伞吗
-l can. -Really?
可以 真的吗
That's amazing.
真不可思议
I had no idea you were an amateur magician.
我不知道你还是个业余魔术师
Hey. Wait. Hey, hey, hey. Hey, I'm talking to you.
嘿 等等 等等 等等 我在跟你聊天耶
Hey, Isabel. I'm--
嘿 伊莎贝 伊莎贝 我在
Jack, listen to me, ! was born a witch, my parents are witches, I'm a witch.
杰克 你听我说 我天生就是一个 女巫”一个货真价实的女巫
-A real witch. -That's right, Isabel.
女巫 很好 伊莎贝
-You go, girl. -lsabel, you tell him.
很好 伊莎贝 太棒了 伊莎贝
That is cool. That's great.
真是一个天才 太棒了
You are very frustrating.
我真是受不了你了
Do you have some Daniel Day-Lewis thing happening here?
你是不是太入戏了呀 伊莎贝
How's it going?
怎么样
I'm leaving.
我要走了
Thank you.
谢谢
Hey there. I have hepatitis C.
路 亲爱的 我有C型肝炎
Isabel? Isabel.
伊莎贝 伊莎贝
Isabel, what's going on? Come back to the party.
伊莎贝 你是怎么了 你快回来嘛
What are you--? Where are you going? What--?
你要去哪啊 你 等等
Wow. That's really cool. Did Props make that?
哇 太棒了 道具师蔡你做的吗
-l keep trying to tell you-- -Can I get your car, miss?
杰克 我一直想告诉你
She doesn't need her car, she has her broomstick.
要你的车吗 不用啦 她有扫曲
-You think I'm nuts, don't you? -Of course not.
你觉得我疯了 是不是
I know plenty of women who carry around collapsible broomsticks.
当然不是 很多女人都会 随身带着折释式扫曲的
-I'll get the car. -It won't be there, I sent it home.
我去帮你拿车 我会让它先回家的
This looks so real. Il can't even see the buttons.
这跟真的一样 没有按钮耶
It is real.
这是真的
Flies too.
它也能飞
Oh, I'd love to see that.
我倒很想看看
-Hang on. -What?
抓紧了 什么
Put me down!
快把我弄下来
I kept trying to tell you.
我一直想告诉你
It's no big deal, Jack.
这只是件小事
-It's no big deal. -This is a huge deal!
只是件小事 这是件大事
We can work this out. It's just who I happen to be.
我只是女巫 你离我远一点
-Get away from me. -What?
没什么大不了的 离远点
You tricked me! You put spells on me!
你骗我 你对我下了贺语
Well, only a few, yes, I did. But I took most of them off.
是的 但只下过几次 不过都解除了
Help! Someone help!
来人呀 救命啊
Jack. I thought this would be okay.
杰克 我以为你能接受呢
How would it be okay?!
我怎么能接受
-I'm a little freaked out now. -l know, but I can't change what I am.
我被吓坏了 但我不能改变原来的我
-Are you crazy? Are you even human? -Jack!
你疯图 你是人吗
-Am I gonna get pregnant? -What?
杰克 ”我会怀孕吗
Because I can't get pregnant right now!
什么 我现在不能怀孕呢
How does this work? Will l get webbed feet?
我的脚会长中吗
You're hurting my feelings.
你这些话很伤人
Shoo! Shoo!
噢
-Shoo? -Shoo!
啊
-Now you're making me angry! -Go! Scat!
你让我生气了 杰克 走开 走开
-You want me to leave? -Yes!
你要我走 对
-Fine!
好吧 好走 好
Goodbye, Jack.
再见了 杰克
You jerk!
你这个大混蛋
Sorry, Mr. Wyatt, I can't find her car.
抱歉 我找不到她的车
So she quit. So what?
她不演了 又怎么样
How's Jack taking all this?
杰克还好吧
Let me tell you guys something. Jack Wyatt's like a jet fighter pilot.
杰克就像战斗机飞行员一样
Nothing rattles him. I'm sure he's just at the gym.
他很强悍 他现在一定正在健身呢
Hey, okay. Stop holding my arm.
好了 好了 别这么用力抓我
Found him picking up pennies out of a shopping-mall water fountain.
这位先生 在打捞喷泉里的铜板
Thank you so much, officer. How much do I tip you for that?
谢谢你 警官 我要给你多少小费
-You don't tip me. -Hey, Jack.
不用给我小费 嘿 杰克
-Hey, all. -Hey, big guy.
大家好 了螺 大人物
-How's it going? -What's up, Jack?
什么事 杰克
-You all right? -Boy.
你还好吗 好哇 是啊
Yeah, I'm all right. I've never been better. Come on.
我好得很 我好得不得了
What's the bottle of ketchup for?
你拿着蕃茄痪干嘛
-Come again? -The....
你说什么 那个
Oh. Forgot to leave it at this diner in Mexico.
哦 我不小心从餐馆带出来的
Don't freak out on us, Jack.
别突然发疯 杰克
-You're fired. -Classic.
你被开除了 真好笑
-Anyone have a light? -Yo.
谁有打火机 我
-l do. -Right here, pal.
我有
Everybody. Let's just calm down.
大家冷静点
We've only shot two episodes. We've got 10 weeks before we air.
我们现在只录了两集 电视剧在十星期后才会播出
-So we recast. Piece of cake. -Next.
所以重新找人 是没问题的 继续讨论吧
I don't know. It'll be hard to find somebody with those scores.
很难找到分数那么高的演员
It's good scores, good scores.
很难哦
-She's a witch. -That's more like it.
她是个女巫
You just keep telling yourself that, man.
你说对了 你能这么想就好了
I'm fine, really.
我没事了
I mean, last night I ate three burritos and smashed every dish in my house.
昨晚我狂吃一顿 重烂了家里所有的盘子
Isabel. You can't let this guy ruin your life.
伊莎贝 你不能让他毁了你的一生
They're recasting your role.
他们在重新找演员呢
They're recasting my role already?
他们这么快就重新找演员
-Well, you quit. -Tough town.
是呀 你不是不演了吗 好现实哦
-l mean, like, what happened? -He said I wasn't human.
到底发生什么事了 他骂我不是人
And he waved a tree branch at me. Like:
而且还拿着树枝来刺我
There must be a solution.
一定有办法解决的
No, there isn't.
没有办法
We're at the Coffee Bean and there is no solution.
我们坐在这里 是一点办法也没有
Il love you, Jack!
我爱你 杰克 我爱你 杰克
Jack, I dreamt about you last night!
杰克 找昨晚梦到你
Jack, remember me? Amber?
杰克 你记得我吗 我是安柏
Oh, my stars.
典 天啊
Darrin's coming home and I haven't even made dinner.
戴伦就快回家了 但我晚饭还没做呢
What?
干嘛
You're great. You want anything?
你很棒
-Thank you. -Thank you very much, that was--
你要什么吗 谢谢 非常谢谢 谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢
Boo! Trick or treat!
不给糖我们就捣蛋
You guys look great.
你们好可爱哦
Happy Halloween.
万圣节快乐
Mommy!
妈妈 妈妈
I'm sorry I don't have any candy.
对不起 我没有糖果
Hi, everyone, and welcome once again to Jeopardy!
欢迎收看 百万大挑战
Another exciting half-hour of answers and questions...
最受欢迎的机智问答节目
...With these categories in our first round of play.
第一回合的题目包括
First off, "Cheese."
第一题 起司
Next, "Things That End In '-Zing.""
第二题 尾音是L的生字
! have no idea where we are.
我不知道我们在哪儿
! mean, I literally could not find Vietnam on a map.
我在地图上找不到越南
And now we're about to die here?
现在却要死在这
! think it's next to Argentina.
越南好像在阿根廷旁边
Well, at least nobody shot at us yet.
是呀 至少没人向我们开枪
Yikes! That's not good.
哎呀 情况不钞
"Yikes."
了网呀
! think the lions are here, Atticus.
狮子被放出来了
And there's Willy, doing his famous Willy Walk.
威利要使出他出名的脚步
Sherpa!
雪巴
We've got to go.
我们得走了
Don't look at me like that. It's the only solution.
别这样看我 这是唯一的办法
Isabel, would you please join me in the dining alcove? Thank you.
伊莎贝 请你到餐厅来一下 谢谢
Daddy?
和爸爸
Something very odd is happening.
我发现了一件怪事情
It's not odd, it's what you predicted. I'm leaving.
并不奇怪 你早就料到了 我要走了
Il can't stop thinking about Iris.
我满脑子想的都是艾莉丝
You were right. 1 don't belong here.
你说的对 我不属于这里
I find myself uninterested in any other woman. Now, that's not natural.
我对其他女人毫无兴趣 这很不正常 你想她有没有可能
-Do you think there's a chance that.... -What?
也是
That she might be a witch?
也许她也是个女巫
Don't be silly.
什么
And she put a spell on me?
她对我施了爱情魔法
Please.
别傻了
Why not? You're a witch. I'm a witch. She could be a witch.
为什么不 你是女巫 我是男巫 她也可能是女巫
I guess she could.
可能是吧
What else could it be?
不然这是怎么回事
Love.
爱情 哦
Isn't there a spell that can make you stop crying?
有没有能让人不器的魔法
No, darling, there isn't.
没有 宝贝
He's idiotic, and yet I find him completely charming.
他很傻 但我却觉得他很迷人
It's been like that since the beginning.
我从一开始就这么觉得
Only now, I also hate him.
不过现在我也很恨他
Love.
这就是爱情
Daddy, what am I gonna do?
爸爸 我该怎么办
Go home.
回家吧
Where's that?
我的家在哪儿
Wherever you've been the happiest.
你觉得最快乐的地方
Perhaps I'll go to Aruba.
也许我会去阿卢巴岛
-Aruba? -But then again, perhaps I won't.
阿卢巴岛 但也许我不会去
! don't know if I'm loving my haircut.
今天我的发型不怎么样 是不怎样
Well, Conan, I can't believe you're bringing this up.
我不敢相信你会提起这件事
No. No. No, no, no. I'm not gonna tell that story. There's no way.
不行 不行 不 我不会说的 好吧
Okay, okay, if you insist.
那你要我说我就说了
It was last June, and I actually cast this witch as a witch...
去年啦 我找来一个 真正的女巫演女巫
..and now brooms make me cry.
现在我看到扫曲就会哭 我每晚都睡不党
I can't sleep, and I don't know what's real or what's the TV show.
分不出现实世界还电视节目
Hi-de-ho!
路 你好
Look what the cat dragged in. Somebody is retaining water.
瞧瞧你这副德性 杰克 太差劲了 太差劲了
Uncle Arthur. It's you.
阿瑟叔叔 是你
Oh, no, you're gonna crack the mirror, aren't you?
哦不 你要弄破镜子 对吧
You watch too much television.
你电视看太多了
-l know you'll do it. You always do. -Don't be silly.
你每次都会弄破镜子的 我知道
Come closer. Do I have something in my teeth right there?
别傻了 杰克 靠近一点 我的齿颖是不是有东西
-Where? -Look!
哪儿 看呀
That was fun!
挺好玩的
She quit. Now, leave me alone.
她不演了 你别烦我
But she was the one.
她真的是你女人
I know, I know. I can't stop thinking about her.
哦 我知道 我忘不了她
-But she's a witch. -Yes, and?
可她是一个女巫呀 那又怎么样呢
-Jack, you're on! -Oh, no, I'm on.
杰克 该你上场了 我得上场了
Go get them, tiger!
快去吧
--revival of the hit series Bewitched.
热门影集 神仙家庭 男主角
You know him from such films as Last Year in Katmandu...
他也曾主演 西藏大疯狂
..An Onion For Willy and Atticus Rex.
前进越南 和 神鬼斗士
Please welcome our good pal, Jack Wyatt!
请欢迎我们的好朋友 杰克
Oh, my God.
嗪 我的天啊
It was a dream.
这是场梦
Thank God.
谢天谢地
No such luck, Jackie boy.
你没这么幸运
Stay back!
哦 离我远一点
Okay, okay. You are not real. You're from the TV show.
你不是真人 你是电视人物 对吧
You have blond highlights...
你拍上一部戏把头发染黄
..and had to wear a girdle on your last movie.
还穿这一件登山服
Who's calling who not real?
你还敢说我不是真人
Okay, I do not believe this. lam not--
我不相信
You are....
你是
-You are real. -Temporarily.
你是真的 这是暂时的
Oh, Uncle Arthur. You're my favorite character.
哦 阿瑟叔叔 我最爱你这个角色
I know.
我知道
What the hell's going on?
这到底是怎么回事
You need help. Your love life's a mess, buddy boy.
你需要帮忙 你简直是一团粳
I know, I'm miserable.
是啊 我真是可怜了
So am I. l have been in reruns for 32 years.
我更惨 你知道吗 我被回放了32年
I need the sizzle of prime time! I need to get this show back on the air.
我又回到黄金时段了 我比你更可怜
Okay, this is very complicated and unsettling, all right?
这整件事太复杂了 知道吗 我一点都不明白
I don't think I understand.
阿瑟叔叔这到底是
Oh. All right.
好吧
Do you want the short version or the long version?
你是让我长话还是短说呢
Keep in mind that the long version is in Aramaic.
长话可以说整整一个星期呢
The short version.
那就短说吧
You got involved with a witch, and when you do that...
当你爱上一个女巫 就一定
.. weird stuff happens.
会发生怪事
-That's it? -Do I have to explain everything?
就这样 是的 每件事都要解释吗
Okay, here's the deal. I'm not real.
好吧 我就直说吧 我不是真的
-lris is a witch. -lris is a witch?
艾莉丝是女巫”艾莉丝是女巫
Don't dwell. And, in my opinion...
别想这么多了 至于你的经纪人
-... that manager of yours, Richie... -What?
瑞奇 什么
isn't even human.
他根本不是人
-Now, where was I? -When?
我说到哪儿
Before you woke up. Oh, right! Who wants to be with a witch?
你醒来之前 没想跟女巫在一起吧
Crazy crap like this would always be happening!
没错 但这种怪事就会发生
And your point is?
你的问题是什么
-The point is, you'd never know. -What?
问题是我永远不知道 不知道什么
Whether you were in love with her, or whether she put a spell on you.
不知道我是真的爱她呢 还是被她施了魔法
Like when you first spotted her in the bookstore. Probably her idea, right?
你在书店跟她搭训 是她的主意吗
No, that was my idea.
不 那是我的主意
-Oh, that's terrible. -l know, I just love to blend.
好难喝峨 我喜欢随便乱调些酒
And when you got down on your knees and you begged her to take the job.
你曾经跪下来求她演珊曼落
What are you saying?
你想说什么
She probably planted the words in your head.
那番话也是她设计的吧
No way, my words.
不是 那是我的真心话
Yeah. What about the nose?
恩对 那她的鼻子呢
Hello? Is that even really her nose?
说不定也不是真的
Of course it's her real nose.
那当然是真的 阿瑟叔叔
Look. Is all's I'm saying is, who wants to be with a witch?
听着 你要搞明白 谁想跟女巫在一起呀
Ido.
我想
She's going home.
她要回家
And once a witch returns home, she can't come back for 100 years.
女巫一回去 要一百年以后才能回来呢
She can't leave.
她不能回去 我需要她
Well, come on, let's go get her.
对 那就回去找她吧 动作快一点
Here we go! Let's go! Let's go get her!
走吧 快走吧 快点
We'd better hurry. She's leaving right this minute.
快点 她马上就会走
We've gotta stop her.
我们得阻止她呀
Remember that episode where you pulled out and almost crashed?
你不能开车 有一集你倒车 差点出车祸 你记得吗
Yes, well, that wasn't exactly me.
是啊 那并不是我
I, personally, am a great driver.
其实我的开车技术是很棒的
Whoopsie doodle!
啊 糟糕透顶
Take it easy!
别这么急嘛 你开慢一点
Can you slow down just a tad?
哦 你 小心点
Is it "Porsche" or is it "Porscha"?
你的车不怎么样 知道吗
Who cares? Watch the road, please. We've gotta get Isabel!
管它呢 看好你的路 我们一定要追上伊莎贝
Oh, all right, party pooper. Let me drive!
好 让我好好开车吧
-There she is! -Where?
她在那 哪儿
Oh, no, she's flying away!
卫 她飞走了
Pedal to the metal, buddy boy!
我要全速前进图
Watch it!
哦 小心
Oh, I'm about to be killed by a fictional character.
我会被一个虚构人物害死的
Yes, you are.
一点也没错
-We're here. -Here. Where?
到了 到了 这几
Where is she?
她在哪儿
Our place. She's at our place.
她在哪儿 她在我们的家
Thank you. Thank you, Uncle Arthur.
谢谢你 阿瑟叔叔 谢谢你
Run to her, you idiot!
快去找她吧 傻小子
Isabel.
伊莎贝
Oh, my God, you're here.
我的天啊 你在这
I'm so happy you're here.
我好高兴 你在这儿
-I'm leaving. -No, no, no, you can't.
我要走了 不 不 不行
You'll be gone forever if you leave.
你一走就永远不回来了
You'll be gone 100 years without being able to come back.
一百年内都不能回来的你知道吗
That's ridiculous. Who told you that?
胡说八道 是谁说的 他说的
Well, what are you doing here if you're leaving?
你真的要走 那你为什么还要来这里呢
l was going home.
我本来要回家
But I don't know where that is.
可是我不知道我的家在哪儿
Home is with me.
我的家就是你的家
-Don't go. Please. -But I'm--
求求你不要走 可是我
-We'll work it out. -We can't.
我们会想办法的 行不通的
Yes, we can.
一定行的
I can't be normal, because I'm a witch.
我是一个女巫 不是正常人
I can't be a witch, because I really wanna be normal.
可是我又非常想当正常人 但这是不可能的
-It's not possible. -Of course it's possible.
当然有可能了
There's tons of other witches who've done it.
有一大堆女巫都这样的
Who?
谁
Well, maybe not tons of other witches, but at least one.
也许没有一大堆 但至少有一个
Samantha.
珊曼莎
Caught between two worlds, and yet completely happy.
是的 她活在两个世界却很开心
She lived happily ever after, in fact.
她从此过着幸福美满的日子
Although there's no way to be sure. She went off the air.
不过她的节目后来停擂了
We'll work it out.
我们会想办法解决的
Don't cry, little witch.
别哭 小女巫
l love you, Samantha.
我爱你 珊曼莎
Isabel.
是伊莎贝
I knew that.
我知道 伊莎贝
I think.
唱
Il love you, Darrin.
我爱你
It just occurred to me, you could have any guy...
我突然想到 你可以拥有
..in the whole world.
世界上任何男人
Oh, but I chose you.
但是我挑中你
Honestly, I think you made a mistake.
老实说 我觉得你挑错人了
If l did, l can always get out of it.
我也可以随时离开你
Now we have things to do.
我们有正事要做
-We have a show to do. -Yes.
我们要拍一部电视剧 是的
And then, maybe after a while, we could get married.
也许过一阵子我们俩个可以结婚
There it is.
我们到了
Good brakes.
来 天啊
Abner, come look! The new neighbors are moving in!
快来看 新邻居搬进来了
Not now, Gladys, I'm busy.
别烦我 我正忙着呢
Yes.
好了
I'm now going to carry you across the threshold.
我要抱着你进大门
Don't you think the front lawn looks a little bare?
你不觉得前院缺了什么吗
No, I don't.
不会呀
But I think it could use a little something.
我觉得可以种一棵树
It's fine the way it is, honey.
这样就挺不错了
Abner! A tree just appeared in the front yard!
快看 他们的前院置出了一棵树